all	O
songs	O
written	O
by	O
m.o.d.	B-GRP
,	O
unless	O
otherwise	O
stated	O

he	O
worked	O
in	O
a	O
bookstore	B-GRP
before	O
becoming	O
a	O
journalist	O
,	O
first	O
for	O
le	B-GRP
devoir	I-GRP
,	O
and	O
then	O
for	O
cité	B-CW
libre	I-CW
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
later	O
became	O
the	O
director	O
.	O

indigenous	O
outlaw	O
musquito	B-PER
defied	O
colonial	O
law	O
and	O
led	O
attacks	O
on	O
settlers	O
.	O

the	O
main	O
contractor	O
was	O
ssangyong	B-CORP
engineering	I-CORP
and	I-CORP
construction	I-CORP
.	O

she	O
became	O
opposed	O
to	O
abortion	O
in	O
1992	O
while	O
attending	O
a	O
bible	B-CW
study	O
and	O
has	O
since	O
spoken	O
out	O
about	O
how	O
abortion	O
has	O
negatively	O
impacted	O
her	O
life	O
.	O

the	B-GRP
guardian	I-GRP
described	O
the	O
album	O
's	O
release	O
as	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
50	O
key	O
events	O
in	O
the	O
history	O
of	O
r&b	O
and	O
hip	O
hop	O
.	O

the	O
gameplay	O
has	O
been	O
described	O
as	O
action	O
heavy	O
,	O
and	O
compared	O
to	O
the	O
ratchet	B-CW
&	I-CW
clank	I-CW
series	O
.	O

mingus	O
left	O
in	O
1951	O
and	O
red	B-PER
mitchell	I-PER
replaced	O
him	O
.	O

it	O
was	O
developed	O
by	O
a	O
team	O
led	O
by	O
former	O
blizzard	B-CORP
entertainment	I-CORP
employees	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
whom	O
had	O
overseen	O
the	O
creation	O
of	O
the	O
diablo	B-CW
series	O
.	O

in	O
the	O
winter	O
months	O
,	O
snowmobile	B-PROD
is	O
also	O
popular	O
.	O

the	O
1988	O
elections	O
were	O
also	O
held	O
on	O
a	O
non	O
party	O
basis	O
,	O
although	O
around	O
30	O
candidates	O
sympathetic	O
to	O
the	O
muslim	B-GRP
brotherhood	I-GRP
were	O
elected	O
.	O

she	O
fronted	O
the	O
band	O
gossip	B-GRP
from	O
its	O
formation	O
in	O
1999	O
until	O
its	O
dissolution	O
in	O
2016	O
.	O

the	O
game	O
uses	O
a	O
battery	O
packed	O
random-access	B-PROD
memory	I-PROD
in	O
order	O
to	O
save	O
progress	O
.	O

in	O
the	O
end	O
the	O
best	O
placed	O
rider	O
was	O
wilfried	B-PER
cretskens	I-PER
who	O
finished	O
61st	O
.	O

of	O
the	O
429	O
delegates	O
who	O
attended	O
,	O
over	O
one	O
third	O
were	O
from	O
the	O
area	O
around	O
wheeling	B-LOC
.	O

the	O
group	O
smith	B-GRP
recorded	O
a	O
version	O
on	O
their	O
1969	O
debut	O
album	O
,	O
sung	O
by	O
gayle	B-PER
mccormick	I-PER

bamboo	O
,	O
like	O
wood	B-PROD
,	O
is	O
a	O
natural	O
composite	B-PROD
material	I-PROD
with	O
a	O
high	O
strength	O
to	O
weight	O
ratio	O
useful	O
for	O
structures	O
.	O

in	O
previous	O
years	O
he	O
had	O
worked	O
with	O
alex	B-PER
cox	I-PER
on	O
the	O
soundtracks	O
of	O
his	O
films	O
sid	B-CW
and	I-CW
nancy	I-CW
and	O
walker	B-CW
in	O
1986	O
and	O
1987	O
.	O

historian	O
françois	B-PER
furet	I-PER
was	O
originally	O
slated	O
to	O
write	O
the	O
introduction	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
died	O
before	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
.	O

it	O
is	O
the	O
main	O
hub	O
of	O
fiji	B-CORP
airways	I-CORP
and	O
its	O
domestic	O
and	O
regional	O
subsidiary	O
fiji	B-CORP
link	I-CORP
.	O

he	O
picked	O
up	O
his	O
dad	O
’s	O
banjo	O
at	O
age	O
8	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
11	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
gibson	B-CORP
banjo	O
endorsement	O
.	O

a	O
term	O
loan	O
is	O
a	O
monetary	O
loan	B-PROD
that	O
is	O
repaid	O
in	O
regular	O
payments	O
over	O
a	O
set	O
period	O
of	O
time	O
.	O

riccardo	B-PER
ghedin	I-PER
/	O
stéphane	B-PER
robert	I-PER
def	O
.	O
arnaud	B-PER
clément	I-PER
/	O
olivier	B-PER
rochus	I-PER
,	O
6	O
–	O
2	O
,	O
5	O
–	O
7	O
,	O
[	O
10	O
–	O
7	O
]	O

many	O
buildings	O
were	O
built	O
in	O
a	O
brick	O
nonplastering	O
style	O
characterized	O
by	O
a	O
special	O
kind	O
of	O
decorative	B-CW
arts	I-CW
using	O
colored	O
,	O
figured	O
bricks	O
,	O
usually	O
yellow	O
and	O
red	O
.	O

the	O
city	O
is	O
also	O
home	O
to	O
via	B-GRP
university	I-GRP
college	I-GRP
which	O
brings	O
a	O
lot	O
of	O
international	O
students	O
to	O
move	O
to	O
this	O
town	O
.	O

refrigerator	B-PROD
,	O
a	O
device	O
used	O
to	O
cool	O
objects	O
or	O
interior	O
spaces	O

vanadzor	O
(	O
)	O
is	O
an	O
urban	O
municipal	O
community	O
and	O
the	O
third	O
largest	O
city	O
in	O
armenia	B-LOC
,	O
serving	O
as	O
the	O
capital	O
of	O
lori	B-LOC
region	I-LOC
in	O
the	O
northern	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
.	O

oakland	O
's	O
defense	O
,	O
anchored	O
by	O
defensive	O
end	O
john	B-PER
matuszak	I-PER
,	O
was	O
punishing	O
.	O

recipes	O
vary	O
slightly	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
dish	O
is	O
basically	O
crème	B-PROD
caramel	I-PROD
made	O
out	O
of	O
eggs	O
and	O
sweetened	O
milk	O
.	O

one	O
maglite	B-CORP
of	O
rechargeable	O
focusing	O
flashlight	O
uses	O
a	O
halogen	O
lamp	O
and	O
produces	O
218	O
lumens	O
.	O

it	O
was	O
also	O
used	O
in	O
the	O
netflix	B-CORP
series	O
stranger	B-CW
things	I-CW
.	O

he	O
played	O
4	O
games	O
for	O
the	O
united	B-CORP
rugby	I-CORP
championship	I-CORP
club	O
.	O

the	O
philosopher	O
and	O
historian	O
,	O
władysław	B-PER
tatarkiewicz	I-PER
,	O
was	O
his	O
grandson	O
.	O

jane	B-PER
fonda	I-PER
–	O
julia	B-CW
as	O
lillian	B-PER
hellman	I-PER

on	O
the	O
first	O
episode	O
of	O
season	O
thirty	O
one	O
of	O
jeopardy!	B-CW
,	O
jeopardy	O
!	O

his	O
work	O
is	O
held	O
in	O
the	O
collections	O
of	O
the	O
j.	B-LOC
paul	I-LOC
getty	I-LOC
museum	I-LOC
,	O
metropolitan	B-LOC
museum	I-LOC
of	I-LOC
art	I-LOC
,	O
museum	B-LOC
of	I-LOC
fine	I-LOC
arts,	I-LOC
houston	I-LOC
,	O
and	O
museum	B-LOC
of	I-LOC
modern	I-LOC
art	I-LOC
.	O

after	O
a	O
long	O
break	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
1996	O
,	O
he	O
issued	O
naposletku...	B-CW
(	O
after	O
all	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
)	O
.	O

she	O
also	O
meets	O
two	O
versions	O
of	O
jesus	B-PER
—	O
a	O
kindly	O
but	O
ineffective	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
who	O
makes	O
a	O
living	O
by	O
posing	O
for	O
an	O
artist	O
depicting	O
him	O
on	O
a	O
cross	O
.	O

the	O
first	O
type	O
was	O
built	O
by	O
hohenzollern	B-CORP
locomotive	I-CORP
works	I-CORP
and	O
baldwin	B-CORP
locomotive	I-CORP
works	I-CORP
in	O
1928	O
and	O
1929	O
respectively	O
.	O

after	O
the	O
association	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
newspapers	O
,	O
léon	B-PER
nicole	I-PER
served	O
as	O
their	O
editor	O
.	O

jeanne	B-PER
marni	I-PER
(	O
1854	O
–	O
1910	O
,	O
france	O
)	O
,	O
nv	O
.	O
&	O
pw	O
.	O

the	O
vendor	O
members	O
sell	O
street	B-PROD
food	I-PROD
or	O
other	O
goods	O
,	O
such	O
as	O
fresh	O
flowers	O
and	O
toys	O
.	O

he	O
played	O
in	O
major	B-CORP
league	I-CORP
baseball	I-CORP
(	O
mlb	O
)	O
for	O
the	O
baltimore	B-GRP
orioles	I-GRP
.	O

welenchiti	O
is	O
served	O
by	O
a	O
railway	O
station	O
on	O
the	O
addis	B-LOC
ababa–djibouti	I-LOC
railway	I-LOC
.	O

the	O
main	O
works	O
were	O
at	O
irlam	B-LOC
.	O

among	O
these	O
peoples	O
turquoise	O
was	O
used	O
in	O
mosaic	B-PROD
inlay	O
,	O
in	O
sculptural	O
works	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
fashioned	O
into	O
toroidal	O
beads	O
and	O
freeform	O
pendants	O
.	O

in	O
1990	O
italian	B-CORP
post	I-CORP
issued	O
a	O
stamp	O
in	O
his	O
honor	O
.	O

the	O
music	O
video	O
for	O
the	O
title	O
track	O
was	O
filmed	O
by	O
canon	B-CORP
inc.	I-CORP
as	O
a	O
campaign	O
for	O
their	O
4k	O
canon	B-PROD
eos	I-PROD
c500	I-PROD
camera	O
.	O

in	O
2017	O
,	O
amy	B-PER
chu	I-PER
began	O
writing	O
the	O
series	O
.	O

guinness	B-CW
world	I-CW
records	I-CW
2002	O
classified	O
it	O
as	O
the	O
most	O
valuable	O
tooth	O
,	O
which	O
would	O
value	O
approximately	O
£	O
25,000	O
(	O
35,700	O
)	O
in	O
late	O
2001	O
.	O

the	O
show	O
makes	O
extensive	O
use	O
of	O
1980s	O
popular	O
music	O
,	O
including	O
nena	B-PER
99	B-CW
luftballons	I-CW
,	O
david	B-PER
bowie	I-PER
,	O
new	B-GRP
order	I-GRP
and	O
eurythmics	B-GRP
among	O
others	O
.	O

mongolia	O
has	O
an	O
embassy	O
in	O
tokyo	B-LOC
,	O
established	O
in	O
1973	O
.	O

in	O
1923	O
,	O
he	O
founded	O
the	O
organization	O
rodobrana	B-GRP
(	O
home	O
guard	O
)	O
,	O
an	O
armed	O
militia	O
.	O

these	O
online	O
features	O
were	O
still	O
considered	O
a	O
breakthrough	O
in	O
video	O
games	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
competing	O
playstation	B-PROD
2	I-PROD
did	O
not	O
ship	O
with	O
a	O
built	O
in	O
network	O
adapter	O
.	O

built	O
in	O
germany	B-LOC
by	O
h.	B-CORP
c.	I-CORP
stülcken	I-CORP
sohn	I-CORP
at	O
steinwerder	B-LOC
,	O
hamburg	B-LOC
.	O

porkins	O
has	O
gained	O
some	O
comedic	O
notoriety	O
due	O
to	O
his	O
size	O
,	O
manner	O
and	O
untimely	O
death	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
spoofed	O
in	O
the	O
family	B-CW
guy	I-CW
episode	O
blue	B-CW
harvest	I-CW
.	O

eulenhald	O
near	O
waldleiningen	B-LOC
,	O
(	O
c	O
.	O
19	O
ha	O
)	O
,	O

when	O
he	O
was	O
freed	O
,	O
he	O
rushed	O
to	O
the	O
court	O
of	O
charles	B-PER
v	I-PER
of	I-PER
france	I-PER
to	O
renew	O
his	O
allegiance	O
and	O
rejoin	O
bertrand	B-PER
du	I-PER
guesclin	I-PER
troops	O
.	O

character	O
has	O
an	O
unlockable	O
alternate	O
livery	B-PROD
.	O

malcolm	B-PER
todd	I-PER
,	O
73	O
,	O
historian	O
and	O
archaeologist	O
.	O

liu	B-PER
wanting	I-PER
sun	B-PER
shengnan	I-PER
6	O
–	O
7	O
(	O
1	O
–	O
7	O
)	O
,	O
6	O
–	O
3	O
,	O
[	O
10	O
–	O
7	O
]	O

during	O
a	O
1981	O
annual	O
review	O
,	O
he	O
uncovered	O
a	O
$	O
50	O
million	O
fraud	O
scheme	O
involving	O
ad	O
powerhouse	O
j.	B-CORP
walter	I-CORP
thompson	I-CORP
.	O

while	O
auditioning	O
for	O
television	O
and	O
film	O
roles	O
,	O
she	O
worked	O
on	O
theatre	B-GRP
productions	O
of	O
romeo	B-CW
and	I-CW
juliet	I-CW
and	O
arsenic	B-CW
and	I-CW
old	I-CW
lace	I-CW
.	O

michel	B-PER
sanchez	I-PER
,	O
who	O
was	O
member	O
of	O
the	O
band	O
deep	B-GRP
forest	I-GRP
,	O
co	O
wrote	O
the	O
lyrics	O
.	O

his	O
last	O
theatrical	O
composition	O
was	O
music	O
for	O
joan	B-CW
the	I-CW
woman	I-CW
,	O
starring	O
geraldine	B-PER
farrar	I-PER
.	O

the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
beat	O
is	O
constructed	O
out	O
of	O
machine	O
gun	O
sprays	O
,	O
nintendo	B-CORP
themes	O
and	O
bottle	O
blows	O
.	O

he	O
is	O
known	O
for	O
presenting	O
the	O
nos	B-CW
journaal	I-CW
from	O
1996	O
till	O
2009	O
.	O

it	O
essentially	O
is	O
a	O
collarless	O
polo	B-PROD
shirt	I-PROD
.	O

july	O
21	O
–	O
mos	B-CORP
burger	I-CORP
was	O
founded	O
.	O

mbali	B-PER
ntuli	I-PER
was	O
appointed	O
as	O
his	O
successor	O
.	O

her	O
brother	O
was	O
the	O
conservative	B-GRP
party	I-GRP
politician	O
rab	B-PER
butler	I-PER
.	O

cross	O
with	O
nail	B-PROD
in	O
evros	B-LOC
regional	I-LOC
unit	I-LOC
/	O
greece	O
]	O
]	O

he	O
served	O
as	O
the	O
head	O
football	O
coach	O
at	O
allegheny	B-GRP
college	I-GRP
from	O
2002	O
to	O
2015	O
,	O
compiling	O
a	O
record	O
of	O
62	O
–	O
79	O
.	O

the	O
game	O
is	O
based	O
upon	O
the	O
fantasy	O
novels	O
nine	B-CW
princes	I-CW
in	I-CW
amber	I-CW
(	O
doubleday	B-CORP
1970	O
)	O
and	O
the	B-CW
guns	I-CW
of	I-CW
avalon	I-CW
(	O
doubleday	O
1972	O
)	O
by	O
roger	B-PER
zelazny	I-PER
.	O

a	O
popular	O
use	O
is	O
rendering	O
an	O
animated	O
3d	O
scene	O
as	O
an	O
adobe	B-CW
flash	I-CW
file	O
.	O

postman	B-CW
pat	I-CW
(	O
1981	O
,	O
1991	O
–	O
1994	O
,	O
1996	O
,	O
2004	O
–	O
2008	O
)	O

pinky	O
wore	O
the	O
same	O
outfit	O
as	O
in	O
her	O
happy	B-CW
days	I-CW
episodes	O
,	O
though	O
her	O
hair	O
was	O
now	O
in	O
a	O
70s	O
style	O
shag	O
cut	O
.	O

they	O
were	O
extensively	O
refurbished	O
between	O
1989	O
and	O
1992	O
by	O
eastleigh	B-CORP
works	I-CORP
,	O
for	O
use	O
on	O
services	O
on	O
the	O
isle	B-LOC
of	I-LOC
wight	I-LOC
island	B-LOC
line,	I-LOC
isle	I-LOC
of	I-LOC
wight	I-LOC
.	O

ac	B-PROD
propulsion	I-PROD
ebox	I-PROD
,	O
a	O
type	O
of	O
automobile	O

a	O
2014	O
rolling	B-CW
stone	I-CW
reader	O
's	O
poll	O
ranked	O
it	O
the	O
group	O
's	O
fourth	O
best	O
song	O
.	O

the	O
philippine	B-GRP
daily	I-GRP
inquirer	I-GRP
is	O
founded	O
and	O
publishes	O
its	O
first	O
issue	O
.	O

he	O
conducted	O
two	O
albums	O
,	O
both	O
for	O
decca	B-CORP
.	O

brian	B-PER
j.	I-PER
smith	I-PER
(	O
born	O
1981	O
)	O
,	O
actor	O
,	O
stargate	B-CW
universe	I-CW
,	O
sense8	B-CW

during	O
the	O
reign	O
of	O
ibn	B-PER
saud	I-PER
he	O
was	O
the	O
most	O
significant	O
non	O
royal	O
official	O
.	O

tithes	O
)	O
is	O
the	O
seventh	O
tractate	O
of	O
zeraim	B-CW
(	O
order	O
of	O
seeds	O
)	O
of	O
the	O
mishnah	B-CW
,	O
tosefta	B-CW
,	O
and	O
the	O
jerusalem	B-CW
talmud	I-CW
.	O

it	O
is	O
located	O
north	O
of	O
elgin	B-LOC
and	O
about	O
south	O
of	O
the	O
washington	B-LOC
border	O
,	O
at	O
an	O
elevation	O
of	O
.	O

established	O
in	O
1972	O
,	O
the	O
pakistan	B-GRP
naval	I-GRP
air	I-GRP
arm	I-GRP
provides	O
fleet	O
air	O
defence	O
,	O
maritime	O
reconnaissance	O
,	O
and	O
anti	O
submarine	O
warfare	O
capability	O
.	O

one	O
was	O
intercepted	O
by	O
iron	B-PROD
dome	I-PROD
;	O
the	O
other	O
fell	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
area	O
near	O
the	O
city	O
.	O

it	O
is	O
the	O
fourth	O
single	O
from	O
the	O
former	O
duo	O
's	O
first	O
extended	B-CW
play	I-CW
bouquet	B-CW
.	O

cooktop	B-PROD
,	O
the	O
top	O
cooking	O
surface	O
on	O
a	O
kitchen	B-PROD
stove	I-PROD

galindians	O
were	O
two	O
distinct	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
extinct	O
,	O
tribes	O
of	O
the	O
balts	B-PER
.	O

made	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
jilin–shulan	B-LOC
railway	I-LOC
in	O
1941	O

he	O
was	O
a	O
member	O
of	O
the	O
federalist	B-GRP
party	I-GRP
.	O

president	O
in	O
:	O
hot	B-CW
shots!	I-CW
part	I-CW
deux	I-CW
(	O
film	O
,	O
1993	O
)	O

randolph	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
nashville	B-LOC
.	O

u.s.	O
swimmer	O
scott	B-PER
weltz	I-PER
finished	O
fifth	O
in	O
2	O
:	O
09.02	O
to	O
hold	O
off	O
his	O
teammate	O
clark	B-PER
burckle	I-PER
(	O
2	O
:	O
09.25	O
)	O
by	O
23	O
hundredths	O
of	O
a	O
second	O
.	O

similar	O
to	O
many	O
other	O
forms	O
of	O
divination	O
,	O
the	O
diviner	O
casts	O
table	B-PROD
salt	I-PROD
crystals	O
into	O
the	O
air	O
and	O
interprets	O
the	O
patterns	O
as	O
it	O
falls	O
to	O
the	O
ground	O
or	O
travels	O
through	O
the	O
air	O
.	O

the	O
main	O
campus	O
of	O
mountains	B-GRP
of	I-GRP
the	I-GRP
moon	I-GRP
university	I-GRP
,	O
a	O
private	O
university	O
,	O
is	O
located	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
center	O
.	O

andrew	O
has	O
also	O
been	O
a	O
member	O
of	O
the	O
dallas	B-GRP
cowboys	I-GRP
,	O
new	B-GRP
york	I-GRP
jets	I-GRP
,	O
philadelphia	B-GRP
eagles	I-GRP
,	O
and	O
minnesota	B-GRP
vikings	I-GRP
.	O

in	O
1979	O
,	O
under	O
her	O
direction	O
,	O
a	O
documentary	O
about	O
simone	B-PER
de	I-PER
beauvoir	I-PER
appeared	O
.	O

emi	B-CORP
,	O
a	O
music	O
and	O
electronics	O
group	O
of	O
companies	O

it	O
is	O
located	O
in	O
the	O
municipality	O
of	O
rakovica	B-LOC
.	O

coffee	B-PROD
would	O
be	O
included	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
manner	O
.	O

the	O
third	O
,	O
scherzo	B-CW
like	O
movement	O
,	O
has	O
an	O
easy	O
spirit	O
yet	O
is	O
full	O
of	O
complex	O
rhythms	O
and	O
interwoven	O
textures	O
.	O

a	O
saddle	B-PROD
chair	I-PROD
encourages	O
this	O
natural	O
posture	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
when	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
while	O
sleeping	O
.	O

the	O
demo	O
was	O
later	O
released	O
on	O
the	O
quadrophenia	B-CW
box	O
set	O
of	O
2011	O
.	O

gogo	O
,	O
a	O
name	O
for	O
a	O
hair	B-PROD
tie	I-PROD

ocean	B-LOC
city	I-LOC
retains	O
its	O
ban	O
but	O
exempts	O
persons	O
with	O
a	O
concealed	O
weapons	O
permit	O
from	O
the	O
ban	O
.	O

the	O
book	O
's	O
sometimes	O
cynical	O
humor	O
has	O
been	O
described	O
as	O
similar	O
to	O
the	B-CORP
onion	I-CORP
.	O

since	O
2008	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
the	O
senior	O
vice	O
president	O
of	O
disney	B-CORP
television	I-CORP
animation	I-CORP
(	O
owned	O
by	O
the	B-GRP
walt	I-GRP
disney	I-GRP
company	I-GRP
)	O
.	O

the	O
song	O
featured	O
chris	B-PER
trousdale	I-PER
from	O
dream	B-GRP
street	I-GRP
and	O
received	O
high	O
rotation	O
on	O
radio	B-CORP
disney	I-CORP
.	O

a	O
statue	O
of	O
benjamin	B-PER
franklin	I-PER
was	O
displayed	O
at	O
the	O
entrance	O
.	O

jorge	B-PER
martínez	I-PER
de	I-PER
hoyos	I-PER
(	O
el	B-CW
abuelo	I-CW
y	I-CW
yo	I-CW
,	O
1993	O
)	O
and	O
ignacio	B-PER
lópez	I-PER
tarso	I-PER
(	O
de	B-CW
pocas,	I-CW
pocas	I-CW
pulgas	I-CW
,	O
2003	O
)	O

in	O
1941	O
she	O
was	O
appointed	O
to	O
the	O
staff	O
of	O
the	O
royal	B-GRP
academy	I-GRP
of	I-GRP
music	I-GRP
where	O
,	O
starting	O
with	O
seven	O
students	O
,	O
she	O
built	O
the	O
drama	O
course	O
to	O
70	O
students	O
.	O

fantasea	O
,	O
a	O
1978	O
surf	O
movie	O
with	O
shaun	B-PER
tomson	I-PER

he	O
also	O
served	O
as	O
a	O
fundraiser	O
and	O
consultant	O
for	O
the	O
democratic	B-CORP
national	I-CORP
committee	I-CORP
.	O

top	O
4	O
:	O
don't	B-CW
stop	I-CW
me	I-CW
now	I-CW
queen	B-GRP
(	O
pop	O
jazz	O
;	O
choreographer	O
:	O
tba	O
)	O

celebration	O
is	O
a	O
compilation	B-CW
album	I-CW
by	O
switzerland	B-LOC
singer	O
dj	B-PER
bobo	I-PER
,	O
released	O
in	O
2002	O
.	O

karta	O
bink	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
commewijne	B-LOC
district	I-LOC
in	O
about	O
1972	O
.	O

hanriot	O
h	O
.	O
230	O
was	O
a	O
france	B-LOC
twin	O
engined	O
advanced	O
trainer	O
.	O

the	O
product	O
range	O
includes	O
bag	B-PROD
and	O
suitcase	B-PROD
.	O

its	O
northern	O
border	O
follows	O
interstate	B-LOC
81	I-LOC
,	O
and	O
its	O
eastern	O
border	O
follows	O
pennsylvania	B-LOC
route	I-LOC
39	I-LOC
.	O

father	O
émile	B-PER
petitot	I-PER
describes	O
his	O
reception	O
in	O
1862	O
.	O

c	O
37b	O
or	O
gulfstream	B-PROD
g550	I-PROD
,	O
a	O
business	O
jet	O

capcom	B-CORP
purchased	O
the	O
intellectual	O
property	O
in	O
2012	O
and	O
provided	O
funding	O
for	O
the	O
project	O
,	O
reimagining	O
it	O
as	O
an	O
action-adventure	B-CW
game	I-CW
for	O
release	O
on	O
multiple	O
platforms	O
.	O

in	O
1985	O
,	O
he	O
tried	O
a	O
comeback	O
with	O
blue	B-GRP
bulls	I-GRP
,	O
but	O
only	O
played	O
in	O
three	O
provincial	O
matches	O
.	O

this	O
chiefly	O
consisted	O
of	O
coal	O
in	O
the	O
area	O
north	O
of	O
llanelli	B-LOC
and	O
around	O
saundersfoot	B-LOC
.	O

he	O
finished	O
third	O
,	O
behind	O
liberal	B-GRP
party	I-GRP
of	I-GRP
canada	I-GRP
nancy	B-PER
karetak-lindell	I-PER
.	O

(	O
cannata	O
stayed	O
until	O
1981	O
,	O
returning	O
for	O
the	O
river	B-CW
of	I-CW
dreams	I-CW
recording	O
sessions	O
in	O
1993	O
.	O

hershey	B-PROD
bar	I-PROD
,	O
their	O
most	O
iconic	O
product	O

in	O
2015	O
the	O
team	O
switched	O
from	O
ktm	B-CORP
to	O
husqvarna	B-CORP
motorcycles	I-CORP
.	O

she	O
attended	O
public	O
schools	O
in	O
worcester	B-LOC
,	O
and	O
went	O
on	O
to	O
attend	O
wellesley	B-GRP
college	I-GRP
in	O
1902	O
.	O

in	O
1988	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
adapted	O
into	O
a	O
funny	B-CW
farm	I-CW
,	O
starring	O
chevy	B-PER
chase	I-PER
.	O

victor	B-PER
svendsen	I-PER
11	O
–	O
7	O
,	O
11	O
–	O
7	O
,	O
8	O
–	O
11	O
,	O
10	O
–	O
12	O
,	O
11	O
–	O
4	O

indian	B-PROD
locomotive	I-PROD
class	I-PROD
wap-7	I-PROD
locomotive	O
powers	O
the	O
train	O
end	O
to	O
end	O
.	O

he	O
made	O
his	O
debut	O
for	O
sogndal	B-GRP
fotball	I-GRP
in	O
a	O
1	O
1	O
draw	O
against	O
ik	B-GRP
start	I-GRP
.	O

for	O
maximum	O
flavor	O
and	O
aroma	O
,	O
as	O
in	O
mulled	B-PROD
wine	I-PROD
,	O
zest	O
is	O
simply	O
cut	O
from	O
the	O
fruit	O
with	O
a	O
knife	O
.	O

after	O
the	O
film	O
's	O
release	O
,	O
the	O
song	O
became	O
a	O
hit	O
and	O
a	O
jazz	B-CW
standard	I-CW
,	O
and	O
has	O
been	O
widely	O
covered	O
.	O

the	O
airport	O
is	O
a	O
hub	O
for	O
both	O
united	B-CORP
airlines	I-CORP
and	O
frontier	B-CORP
airlines	I-CORP
and	O
a	O
base	O
for	O
southwest	B-CORP
airlines	I-CORP
.	O

the	O
album	O
features	O
six	O
different	O
covers	O
,	O
depicting	O
each	O
of	O
the	O
various	O
band	O
members	O
death	B-PROD
mask	I-PROD
.	O

in	O
2012	O
,	O
the	O
chevrolet	B-PROD
cobalt	I-PROD
was	O
added	O
to	O
the	O
production	O
line	O
.	O

goya	O
learned	O
from	O
these	O
sources	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
rembrandt	B-PER
,	O
some	O
of	O
whose	O
prints	O
he	O
owned	O
.	O

torchlight	B-CW
iii	I-CW
,	O
a	O
2020	O
action	O
role	O
playing	O
game	O

he	O
moved	O
to	O
peru	B-LOC
for	O
eight	O
years	O
.	O

deutch	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
los	B-LOC
angeles	I-LOC
,	O
california	B-LOC
,	O
to	O
actress	O
lea	B-PER
thompson	I-PER
and	O
director	O
howard	B-PER
deutch	I-PER
.	O

lau	O
would	O
later	O
turn	O
down	O
the	O
role	O
,	O
and	O
wang	B-PER
xueqi	I-PER
was	O
cast	O
instead	O
.	O

he	O
moved	O
to	O
stockport	B-GRP
county	I-GRP
f.c.	I-GRP
,	O
playing	O
50	O
times	O
before	O
joining	O
tranmere	B-GRP
rovers	I-GRP
f.c.	I-GRP
.	O

horatio	B-PER
allen	I-PER
,	O
designed	O
world	O
's	O
first	O
articulated	B-PROD
locomotive	I-PROD
in	O
1832	O

for	O
the	O
following	O
year	O
a	O
new	O
car	O
,	O
the	O
ferrari	B-PROD
412	I-PROD
t2	I-PROD
came	O
out	O
which	O
received	O
many	O
changes	O
that	O
aided	O
both	O
aero	O
and	O
safety	O
.	O

it	O
was	O
sung	O
then	O
by	O
john	B-PER
henry	I-PER
johnstone	I-PER
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
later	O
a	O
favourite	O
piece	O
of	O
charles	B-PER
incledon	I-PER
.	O

he	O
played	O
for	O
the	O
miami	B-GRP
dolphins	I-GRP
in	O
1966	O
.	O

the	O
south	O
gallery	O
was	O
extended	O
to	O
the	O
east	O
end	O
and	O
the	O
pulpit	B-PROD
,	O
by	O
then	O
three	O
decker	O
,	O
was	O
relocated	O
to	O
the	O
centre	O
of	O
the	O
nave	O
aisle	O
at	O
the	O
east	O
end	O
.	O

#	O
runaway	B-CW
(	O
del	B-PER
shannon	I-PER
,	O
max	B-PER
crook	I-PER
)	O
–	O
2	O
:	O
19	O

in	O
2010	O
,	O
sony	B-GRP
pictures	I-GRP
television	I-GRP
,	O
the	O
show	O
's	O
production	O
company	O
,	O
released	O
an	O
adaptation	O
for	O
the	O
iphone	B-PROD
,	O
ipod	B-PROD
touch	I-PROD
,	O
and	O
ipad	B-PROD
.	O

starring	O
bing	B-PER
crosby	I-PER
and	O
dorothy	B-PER
lamour	I-PER
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
musical	B-CW
film	I-CW
directed	O
by	O
a.	B-PER
edward	I-PER
sutherland	I-PER
.	O

it	O
is	O
owned	O
and	O
operated	O
by	O
tüpraş	B-CORP
,	O
the	O
country	O
's	O
only	O
oil	O
refiner	O
with	O
four	O
refineries	O
.	O

a	O
recipe	O
is	O
a	O
set	O
of	O
instructions	O
that	O
describes	O
how	O
to	O
prepare	O
or	O
make	O
something	O
,	O
especially	O
a	O
dish	B-PROD
of	O
prepared	O
food	O
.	O

liverpool	B-LOC
also	O
suffered	O
severely	O
,	O
with	O
many	O
shipwrecks	O
and	O
structural	O
damage	O
resulting	O
from	O
strong	O
winds	O
.	O
120	O
people	O
died	O
as	O
a	O
result	O
of	O
such	O
accidents	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
alone	O
.	O

#	O
love	B-CW
for	I-CW
sale	I-CW
(	O
cole	B-PER
porter	I-PER
)	O
7	O
:	O
00	O

colecovision	O
's	O
main	O
competitor	O
was	O
the	O
less	O
commercially	O
successful	O
atari	B-PROD
5200	I-PROD
.	O

the	O
name	O
was	O
not	O
used	O
for	O
several	O
years	O
before	O
being	O
reused	O
for	O
the	O
ibm	B-PROD
pc	I-PROD
series	I-PROD
in	O
the	O
90s	O
and	O
early	O
2000s	O
.	O

he	O
was	O
a	O
founding	O
member	O
of	O
the	O
société	B-GRP
française	I-GRP
de	I-GRP
photographie	I-GRP
.	O

the	O
mantua	B-PROD
or	O
manteau	O
was	O
a	O
new	O
fashion	O
that	O
arose	O
in	O
the	O
1680s	O
.	O

the	O
top	O
goalscorer	O
was	O
craig	B-PER
brewster	I-PER
,	O
who	O
finished	O
the	O
season	O
with	O
20	O
goals	O
.	O

it	O
was	O
released	O
on	O
harvest	B-CORP
/	O
emi	O
as	O
a	O
single	B-CW
in	O
1988	O
.	O

it	O
was	O
later	O
the	O
home	O
field	O
of	O
the	O
calgary	B-GRP
vipers	I-GRP
baseball	O
team	O
of	O
the	O
north	B-GRP
american	I-GRP
league	I-GRP
.	O

they	O
each	O
got	O
a	O
sandpit	O
and	O
a	O
vacuum	B-PROD
cleaner	I-PROD
each	O
.	O

jagertee	O
(	O
also	O
jägertee	O
)	O
is	O
an	O
alcoholic	O
punch	O
historically	O
made	O
by	O
mixing	O
stroh	B-CORP
with	O
spiced	O
black	B-PROD
tea	I-PROD
.	O

the	O
lead	O
single	O
,	O
la	B-CW
puerta	I-CW
del	I-CW
cielo	I-CW
/	I-CW
seven	I-CW
lives	I-CW
,	O
is	O
a	O
fusion	O
of	O
modern	O
and	O
classical	O
elements	O
.	O

young	O
has	O
stated	O
in	O
concert	O
that	O
he	O
wrote	O
the	O
song	O
while	O
studying	O
history	O
in	O
high	O
school	O
in	O
winnipeg	B-LOC
.	O

it	O
is	O
also	O
used	O
as	O
food	O
or	O
a	O
garnish	B-PROD
.	O

the	O
lifeboat	O
was	O
built	O
in	O
1923	O
by	O
j.	B-CORP
samuel	I-CORP
white	I-CORP
at	O
cowes	B-LOC
on	O
the	O
isle	B-LOC
of	I-LOC
wight	I-LOC
.	O

in	O
1799	O
he	O
took	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
reduction	O
of	O
the	O
island	O
of	O
sri	B-LOC
lanka	I-LOC
.	O

au	O
jardin	O
de	O
l	O
enfance	O
,	O
6	O
pieces	O
after	O
l'art	B-CW
d'être	I-CW
grand-père	I-CW
by	O
victor	B-PER
hugo	I-PER
.	O

her	O
artworks	O
on	O
ebay	B-CORP
offer	O
recreations	O
of	O
historic	O
photographs	O
,	O
each	O
incorporating	O
an	O
implausible	O
garment	O
as	O
the	O
main	O
event	O
.	O

however	O
,	O
it	O
had	O
changed	O
its	O
shape	O
to	O
the	O
hourglass	O
silhouette	O
that	O
is	O
even	O
now	O
considered	O
typical	O
both	O
for	O
corsets	O
and	O
for	O
victorian	B-PROD
fashion	I-PROD
.	O

on	O
telegram	B-CW
,	O
a	O
white	O
supremacist	O
channel	O
encouraged	O
members	O
to	O
distribute	O
the	O
propaganda	O
.	O

jordan	O
also	O
played	O
the	O
ex	O
boyfriend	O
in	O
lily	B-PER
allen	I-PER
music	O
video	O
smile	B-CW
.	O

the	O
race	O
started	O
in	O
compiègne	B-LOC
and	O
finished	O
in	O
roubaix	B-LOC
.	O

zarm	O
–	O
a	O
lunar	B-CW
rescue	I-CW
clone	O
(	O
bbc	O
only	O
)	O

grange	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
football	O
player	O
to	O
appear	O
on	O
a	O
box	O
of	O
wheaties	B-PROD
.	O

he	O
is	O
currently	O
under	O
a	O
contract	O
with	O
tvb	B-CORP
.	O

he	O
graduated	O
from	O
brown	B-GRP
university	I-GRP
in	O
1822	O
,	O
tutored	O
there	O
until	O
1824	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
left	O
to	O
study	O
law	O
in	O
windham	B-LOC
,	O
connecticut	B-LOC
.	O

cream	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
butter	O
factory	O
at	O
wowan	B-LOC
.	O

guardians	B-CW
of	I-CW
the	I-CW
galaxy	I-CW
–	O
stephane	B-PER
ceretti	I-PER
,	O
nicolas	B-PER
aithadi	I-PER
,	O
jonathan	B-PER
fawkner	I-PER
,	O
and	O
paul	B-PER
corbould	I-PER

his	O
films	O
cheerful	O
,	O
unpretentious	O
appeal	O
make	O
them	O
the	O
direct	O
descendants	O
of	O
those	O
made	O
a	O
generation	O
earlier	O
by	O
george	B-PER
formby	I-PER
.	O

malone	O
attended	O
the	O
university	B-GRP
of	I-GRP
louisville	I-GRP
,	O
where	O
he	O
played	O
baseball	O
.	O

the	O
classic	O
tree	O
paint	O
is	O
black	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
is	O
based	O
on	O
an	O
asphalt	B-PROD
emulsion	O
.	O

digati	O
put	O
$	O
50,000	O
into	O
a	O
variable	O
life	O
insurance	O
policy	O
by	O
new	B-CORP
york	I-CORP
life	I-CORP
insurance	I-CORP
company	I-CORP
and	O
wanted	O
a	O
return	O
of	O
$	O
198,303.88	O
.	O

because	O
airliner	B-PROD
fly	O
at	O
very	O
high	O
altitudes	O
,	O
the	O
cabin	O
must	O
be	O
pressurized	O
to	O
provide	O
a	O
safe	O
quantity	O
of	O
breathable	O
oxygen	O
to	O
passengers	O
and	O
crew	O
.	O

the	O
ashmolean	B-LOC
museum	I-LOC
in	O
oxford	B-LOC
has	O
a	O
further	O
17	O
landscape	O
drawings	O
.	O

charles	B-PER
the	I-PER
bold	I-PER
confirmed	O
him	O
in	O
these	O
functions	O
and	O
trusted	O
him	O
with	O
diplomatic	O
treaties	O
and	O
negotiations	O
.	O

in	O
2014	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
cameo	O
appearance	O
in	O
the	O
film	O
dumb	B-CW
and	I-CW
dumber	I-CW
to	I-CW
,	O
starring	O
jim	B-PER
carrey	I-PER
and	O
jeff	B-PER
daniels	I-PER
.	O

it	O
was	O
the	O
county	B-LOC
seat	I-LOC
from	O
1885	O
to	O
1919	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
government	O
moved	O
to	O
the	O
current	O
county	O
seat	O
of	O
finley	B-LOC
.	O

professional	O
wrestler	O
bret	B-PER
hart	I-PER
made	O
a	O
cameo	O
as	O
himself	O
,	O
animated	O
in	O
his	O
pink	O
wrestling	O
outfit	O
.	O

her	O
brother	O
jackie	B-PER
levy	I-PER
served	O
as	O
mayor	O
of	O
beit	B-LOC
she'an	I-LOC
for	O
the	O
likud	B-GRP
.	O

laidback	B-PER
luke	I-PER
my	O
g.o.d.	O
(	O
tom	O
stephan	O
mix	O
)	O
[	O
mixmash	O
/	O
bitrate	O
]	O
2010	O

the	O
emotional	O
performance	O
was	O
accompanied	O
by	O
audiences	O
holding	O
lighter	B-PROD
.	O

crimefighters	O
various	O
versions	O
produced	O
by	O
itv	B-CORP
granada	I-CORP
,	O
yorkshire	B-CORP
television	I-CORP
,	O
itv	B-CORP
border	I-CORP
and	O
itv	B-CORP
central	I-CORP

is	O
a	O
manufacturer	O
of	O
coffee	B-PROD
and	O
tea	B-PROD
products	O
in	O
kōbe	B-LOC
,	O
hyōgo	B-LOC
prefecture	I-LOC
.	O

public	O
transport	O
is	O
integrated	O
into	O
the	O
verkehrsverbund	B-GRP
rhein-neckar	I-GRP
,	O
whose	O
fares	O
therefore	O
apply	O
.	O

the	O
kola	O
nut	O
is	O
also	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	B-CW
color	I-CW
purple	I-CW
by	O
alice	B-PER
walker	I-PER
,	O
although	O
it	O
is	O
spelled	O
cola	O
.	O

poe	O
lived	O
in	O
baltimore	B-LOC
for	O
a	O
time	O
and	O
is	O
buried	O
there	O
.	O

he	O
made	O
it	O
through	O
the	O
pre	O
selection	O
,	O
but	O
lost	O
out	O
to	O
ferdinand	B-PER
pauwels	I-PER
who	O
won	O
first	O
prize	O
.	O

throughout	O
the	O
album	O
,	O
the	O
group	O
blends	O
their	O
brand	O
of	O
intelligence	O
,	O
reflection	O
and	O
positivity	O
with	O
humorous	O
anecdote	B-CW
.	O

he	O
then	O
went	O
on	O
to	O
play	O
for	O
fc	B-GRP
auch	I-GRP
gers	I-GRP
between	O
2006	O
and	O
2008	O
.	O

october	O
12	O
–	O
joel	B-PER
digregorio	I-PER
,	O
67	O
,	O
keyboardist	O
for	O
charlie	B-PER
daniels	I-PER
.	O
(	O
car	O
accident	O
)	O

garnier	B-PROD
is	O
a	O
division	O
of	O
the	O
l	O
oréal	O
group	O
which	O
sells	O
hair	O
care	O
products	O
.	O

perry	O
entered	O
the	O
stadium	O
riding	O
atop	O
a	O
large	O
,	O
golden	O
mechanical	O
lion	O
,	O
opening	O
her	O
set	O
with	O
a	O
performance	O
of	O
roar	B-CW
.	O

mia	B-PER
kirshner	I-PER
(	O
born	O
1975	O
)	O
,	O
actress	O
,	O
writer	O
and	O
social	O
activist	O

in	O
2001	O
,	O
16	O
year	O
old	O
kyle	B-PER
busch	I-PER
dominated	O
the	O
race	O
but	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
fuel	O
with	O
20	O
laps	O
to	O
go	O
.	O

in	O
1989	O
george	B-PER
lopez	I-PER
also	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
school	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
speech	O
to	O
a	O
class	O
.	O

meteor	B-CW
garden	I-CW
using	O
on	O
the	O
word	O
gardener	O

she	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
faculty	O
at	O
university	B-GRP
of	I-GRP
oregon	I-GRP
for	O
over	O
two	O
decades	O
.	O

the	O
flight	B-PROD
suit	I-PROD
(	O
fdu	O
)	O
features	O
subdued	O
cloth	O
rank	O
insignia	O
sewn	O
onto	O
the	O
shoulders	O
.	O

the	O
airport	O
's	O
simultaneous	O
remote	O
location	O
and	O
close	O
proximity	O
to	O
the	O
dallas–fort	B-LOC
worth	I-LOC
metroplex	I-LOC
were	O
major	O
factors	O
in	O
the	O
company	O
's	O
decision	O
to	O
conduct	O
experiments	O
there	O
.	O

the	O
line	O
was	O
managed	O
by	O
the	O
east	B-CORP
japan	I-CORP
railway	I-CORP
company	I-CORP
(	O
jr	O
east	O
)	O
from	O
1987	O
.	O

hamamatsu	O
is	O
a	O
member	O
of	O
the	O
world	B-GRP
health	I-GRP
organization	I-GRP
’s	O
alliance	B-GRP
for	I-GRP
healthy	I-GRP
cities	I-GRP
(	O
afhc	O
)	O
.	O

piton	B-PROD
,	O
a	O
metal	O
spike	O
to	O
aid	O
climbing	O

ekeroth	O
joined	O
the	O
sweden	B-GRP
democrats	I-GRP
in	O
2006	O
.	O

it	O
peaked	O
at	O
number	O
one	O
on	O
the	O
oricon	B-CORP
chart	O
.	O

dan	B-PER
baron	I-PER
cohen	I-PER
(	O
born	O
1957	O
)	O
,	O
playwright	O
and	O
community	O
theatre	O
director	O

based	O
on	O
pictures	B-CW
from	I-CW
the	I-CW
insects'	I-CW
life	I-CW
by	O
karel	B-PER
čapek	I-PER
and	O
josef	B-PER
čapek	I-PER

the	O
island	O
is	O
north	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
's	O
capital	O
,	O
malé	B-LOC
.	O

the	O
series	O
is	O
participated	O
in	O
by	O
multiple	O
manufacturers	O
,	O
including	O
jaguar	B-GRP
racing	I-GRP
,	O
audi	B-CORP
,	O
nissan	B-CORP
,	O
bmw	B-CORP
and	O
mahindra	B-CORP
&	I-CORP
mahindra	I-CORP
.	O

panagi	O
is	O
a	O
product	O
of	O
olympiakos	B-GRP
nicosia	I-GRP
fc	I-GRP
academies	O
and	O
in	O
2010	O
he	O
was	O
promoted	O
to	O
the	O
men	O
's	O
team	O
by	O
coach	O
pambos	B-PER
christodoulou	I-PER
.	O

pozdrav	O
milici	O
stojadinović	O
srpkinji	O
,	O
biography	O
(	O
prometej	O
,	O
novi	B-LOC
sad	I-LOC
,	O
2019	O
)	O

the	O
book	O
moves	O
on	O
to	O
marcellin	B-PER
berthelot	I-PER
who	O
in	O
1864	O
claimed	O
to	O
have	O
found	O
petroleum	O
like	O
hydrocarbons	O
in	O
a	O
meteorite	O
found	O
near	O
orgueil	B-LOC
.	O

her	O
film	O
career	O
includes	O
roles	O
in	O
the	B-CW
greek	I-CW
tycoon	I-CW
and	O
cliff	B-PER
twemlow	I-PER
.	O

walmart	B-CORP
briefly	O
entered	O
the	O
market	O
as	O
well	O
,	O
but	O
withdrew	O
in	O
2005	O
and	O
now	O
has	O
a	O
cross	O
promotional	O
agreement	O
with	O
netflix	B-CORP
.	O

it	O
includes	O
over	O
100	O
species	O
of	O
annual	O
and	O
perennial	O
herb	B-PROD
which	O
bear	O
colorful	O
flowers	O
in	O
shades	O
of	O
red	O
to	O
purple	O
and	O
white	O
.	O

he	O
tries	O
to	O
obtain	O
his	O
pension	B-PROD
money	O
,	O
but	O
all	O
his	O
attempts	O
are	O
futile	O
.	O

state	O
legislators	O
had	O
already	O
indicated	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
support	O
the	O
incumbent	O
,	O
frank	B-PER
j.	I-PER
cannon	I-PER
for	O
reelection	O
.	O

naubakht	B-PER
(	O
9th	O
century	O
)	O
,	O
designer	O
of	O
the	O
city	O
of	O
baghdad	B-LOC

kiip	O
is	O
a	O
mobile	O
advertising	B-CORP
network	I-CORP
.	O

the	O
game	O
was	O
named	O
for	O
the	O
local	O
refrigerator	B-PROD
production	O
.	O

there	O
are	O
daily	O
flights	O
of	O
the	O
airbus	B-PROD
a300-600st	I-PROD
beluga	I-PROD
transport	O
aircraft	O
of	O
airbus	B-CORP
wings	O
from	O
broughton	B-LOC
for	O
the	O
smaller	O
aircraft	O
.	O

he	O
presented	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
spain	B-LOC
monarchs	O
,	O
though	O
by	O
then	O
the	O
young	O
were	O
lost	O
and	O
the	O
female	O
had	O
died	O
.	O

he	O
joined	O
cardiff	B-GRP
rfc	I-GRP
for	O
the	O
1990	O
/	O
91	O
season	O
.	O

the	O
recording	O
by	O
christopher	B-PER
hogwood	I-PER
conducting	O
the	O
academy	B-GRP
of	I-GRP
ancient	I-GRP
music	I-GRP
also	O
omits	O
a	O
harpsichord	O
melody	O
in	O
the	O
third	O
movement	O
.	O

as	O
of	O
2008	O
,	O
the	O
optare	B-PROD
solo	I-PROD
is	O
a	O
common	O
type	O
of	O
midibus	O
found	O
on	O
smaller	O
schemes	O
.	O

kathy	B-PER
jordan	I-PER
and	O
paula	B-PER
smith	I-PER
were	O
the	O
defending	O
champions	O
but	O
lost	O
in	O
the	O
final	O
6	O
–	O
4	O
,	O
4	O
–	O
6	O
,	O
6	O
–	O
2	O
against	O
barbara	B-PER
potter	I-PER
and	O
sharon	B-PER
walsh	I-PER
.	O

boller	O
was	O
the	O
defensive	O
line	O
coach	O
for	O
the	O
dallas	B-GRP
cowboys	I-GRP
of	O
the	O
national	B-CORP
football	I-CORP
league	I-CORP
(	O
nfl	O
)	O
from	O
1996	O
to	O
1997	O
.	O

he	O
started	O
his	O
career	O
in	O
special	O
effects	O
in	O
1978	O
on	O
superman	B-CW
.	O

boeing	O
737	O
800	O
of	O
skymark	B-CORP
airlines	I-CORP
at	O
the	O
airport	O
]	O
]	O

since	O
2006	O
,	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
published	O
in	O
tabloid	B-GRP
format	O
.	O

on	O
rotten	B-CORP
tomatoes	I-CORP
,	O
the	O
film	O
currently	O
holds	O
a	O
score	O
of	O
34	O
%	O
and	O
an	O
average	O
rating	O
of	O
3.69	O
/	O
10	O
based	O
on	O
32	O
reviews	O
.	O

the	O
question	O
involves	O
scheduling	O
a	O
series	O
of	O
sports	B-GRP
team	I-GRP
such	O
that	O
:	O

the	O
procurement	O
of	O
the	O
leopard	B-PROD
2	I-PROD
system	O
started	O
in	O
1991	O
.	O

raced	O
on	O
turf	O
over	O
a	O
distance	O
of	O
one	O
mile	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
open	O
to	O
horses	O
three	O
year	O
olds	O
and	O
up	O
of	O
either	O
gender	O
who	O
were	O
bred	O
in	O
the	O
state	O
of	O
california	B-LOC
.	O

the	O
effect	O
is	O
similar	O
to	O
a	O
muffin	O
shaped	O
,	O
caramelized	O
croissant	B-PROD
.	O

dragon	B-CW
reviewers	O
gave	O
the	O
game	O
5	O
out	O
of	O
5	O
stars	O
.	O

nelson	O
had	O
been	O
inspired	O
by	O
as	B-CW
we	I-CW
may	I-CW
think	I-CW
,	O
a	O
popular	O
1945	O
essay	O
by	O
vannevar	B-PER
bush	I-PER
.	O

the	O
papal	B-CW
bull	I-CW
issued	O
which	O
banned	O
this	O
practice	O
was	O
often	O
misinterpreted	O
as	O
prohibition	O
against	O
human	O
dissection	O
.	O

citigroup	B-CORP
private	O
banking	O
arm	O
raised	O
an	O
additional	O
$	O
415	O
million	O
in	O
equity	O
for	O
the	O
project	O
from	O
high-net-worth	B-PER
individual	I-PER
who	O
invested	O
$	O
1	O
million	O
to	O
$	O
5	O
million	O
each	O
.	O

sharzy	O
was	O
born	O
on	O
the	O
island	O
of	O
simbo	B-LOC
in	O
the	O
western	B-LOC
province	I-LOC
.	O

however	O
,	O
other	O
establishments	O
,	O
such	O
as	O
the	O
b.	B-CORP
dalton	I-CORP
bookstore	O
,	O
clothing	O
stores	O
,	O
and	O
shoe	O
stores	O
,	O
started	O
to	O
attract	O
tourists	O
to	O
the	O
area	O
.	O

it	O
is	O
named	O
for	O
william	B-PER
john	I-PER
wills	I-PER
of	O
the	O
burke	B-GRP
and	I-GRP
wills	I-GRP
expedition	I-GRP
.	O

it	O
is	O
now	O
a	O
nonprofit	O
museum	O
operated	O
by	O
historic	B-GRP
new	I-GRP
england	I-GRP
and	O
open	O
to	O
the	O
public	O
several	O
days	O
a	O
year	O
.	O

singer	O
songwriter	O
lorde	B-PER
has	O
two	O
long	O
listed	O
songs	O
.	O

he	O
competed	O
in	O
the	O
2015	O
season	O
of	O
last	B-CW
comic	I-CW
standing	I-CW
,	O
earning	O
a	O
spot	O
in	O
the	O
top	O
10	O
contestants	O
.	O

anupama	B-PER
kumar	I-PER
joined	O
the	O
team	O
to	O
essay	O
an	O
important	O
role	O
.	O

he	O
graduated	O
from	O
the	O
colorado	B-GRP
school	I-GRP
of	I-GRP
mines	I-GRP
in	O
1984	O
.	O

after	O
1884	O
,	O
he	O
worked	O
at	O
his	O
father	O
's	O
studios	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
vienna	B-LOC
state	I-LOC
opera	I-LOC
.	O

it	O
is	O
owned	O
and	O
operated	O
by	O
the	O
norddeutscher	B-CORP
rundfunk	I-CORP
public	O
broadcasting	O
service	O
,	O
but	O
open	O
to	O
competitors	O
,	O
too	O
.	O

the	O
activation	O
by	O
light	O
can	O
be	O
done	O
with	O
very	O
high	O
spatiotemporal	O
precision	O
in	O
the	O
lesion	O
site	O
,	O
leaving	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
patient	B-PER
body	O
unaffected	O
.	O

major	O
recognition	O
came	O
in	O
1986	O
with	O
the	O
production	O
of	O
jean-baptiste	B-PER
lully	I-PER
atys	B-CW
at	O
the	O
opéra-comique	B-GRP
in	O
paris	B-LOC
.	O

during	O
his	O
rule	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
communal	O
clashes	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
of	O
khambhat	B-LOC
and	O
a	O
congregational	O
mosque	O
was	O
damaged	O
.	O

james	O
granted	O
further	O
charters	O
in	O
1608	O
and	O
1614	O
,	O
as	O
did	O
charles	B-PER
ii	I-PER
of	I-PER
england	I-PER
in	O
1668	O
and	O
1684	O
.	O

2009	O
:	O
tatoue-moi	B-CW
,	O
l	O
assasymphonie	O
and	O
other	O
songs	O
mozart,	B-CW
l'opéra	I-CW
rock	I-CW

it	O
was	O
based	O
on	O
the	O
forbidden	B-CW
colors	I-CW
by	O
yukio	B-PER
mishima	I-PER
.	O

miguel	B-PER
hernández	I-PER
(	O
el	O
rayo	O
que	O
no	O
cesa	O
)	O

sliced	O
meat	O
,	O
potatoes	O
,	O
sliced	O
plantain	B-PROD
,	O
yam	O
,	O
kelp	O
,	O
cabbage	O
,	O
and	O
celery	O
.	O

kjosevski	O
joined	O
f.k.	B-GRP
željezničar	I-GRP
sarajevo	I-GRP
youth	O
academy	O
in	O
2005	O
and	O
came	O
through	O
all	O
youth	O
categories	O
.	O

he	O
also	O
rewarded	O
cooperative	O
tribal	O
leaders	O
with	O
trips	O
to	O
washington,	B-LOC
d.c.	I-LOC
,	O
and	O
offered	O
bribes	O
.	O

for	O
service	O
to	O
conservation	O
and	O
the	O
environment	O
through	O
a	O
range	O
of	O
organisations	O
in	O
the	O
north	B-LOC
sydney	I-LOC
region	O
.	O

gibson	O
was	O
educated	O
at	O
harrow	B-GRP
school	I-GRP
,	O
where	O
he	O
played	O
in	O
the	O
cricket	O
team	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
trinity	B-LOC
college	I-LOC
.	O

the	O
episodes	O
of	O
the	O
vampire	B-CW
knight	I-CW
anime	B-CW
adaptation	O
is	O
based	O
on	O
the	O
manga	B-CW
series	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
name	O
written	O
by	O
matsuri	B-PER
hino	I-PER
.	O

r.e.m.	B-GRP
–	O
imitation	B-CW
of	I-CW
life	I-CW
,	O
everybody	B-CW
hurts	I-CW
,	O
man	B-CW
on	I-CW
the	I-CW
moon	I-CW
(	O
hp	O
16	O
:	O
15	O
)	O

the	O
long	B-CORP
beach	I-CORP
naval	I-CORP
shipyard	I-CORP
was	O
established	O
in	O
1943	O
and	O
closed	O
in	O
1997	O
,	O
employing	O
over	O
16,000	O
people	O
at	O
its	O
peak	O
in	O
1945	O
.	O

as	O
of	O
2017	O
it	O
operates	O
from	O
a	O
mailing	O
address	O
in	O
coeur	B-LOC
d'alene	I-LOC
.	O

such	O
pottery	O
is	O
associated	O
with	O
the	O
production	O
,	O
storage	O
and	O
transport	O
of	O
table	B-PROD
salt	I-PROD
.	O

she	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
only	O
female	O
poets	O
praised	O
by	O
the	O
prince	O
of	O
poets	O
,	O
pierre	B-PER
de	I-PER
ronsard	I-PER
and	O
she	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
earliest	O
female	O
erotic	O
poets	O
.	O

#	O
nice	B-CW
work	I-CW
if	I-CW
you	I-CW
can	I-CW
get	I-CW
it	I-CW
(	O
george	B-PER
gershwin	I-PER
,	O
ira	B-PER
gershwin	I-PER
)	O
–	O
2	O
:	O
38	O

linus	B-PER
pauling	I-PER
–	O
chemist	O
,	O
biochemist	O
,	O
peace	O
activist	O
,	O
author	O
,	O
educator	O

the	O
bulk	O
of	O
the	O
locality	O
is	O
used	O
for	O
growing	O
sugarcane	B-PROD
and	O
tropical	O
fruit	O
,	O
while	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
locality	O
(	O
particularly	O
surrounding	O
the	O
creeks	O
)	O
is	O
left	O
as	O
swampy	O
wetlands	O
.	O

crop	O
damage	O
in	O
okayama	B-LOC
prefecture	I-LOC
was	O
estimated	O
at	O
¥	O
90	O
million	O
.	O

a	O
sega	B-PROD
mega	I-PROD
drive	I-PROD
version	O
was	O
planned	O
but	O
never	O
released	O
.	O

he	O
was	O
also	O
a	O
shareholder	O
in	O
the	O
surrey	B-CORP
iron	I-CORP
railway	I-CORP
.	O

they	O
are	O
said	O
to	O
have	O
placed	O
a	O
car	O
bomb	O
in	O
his	O
volkswagen	B-PROD
beetle	I-PROD
.	O

the	O
park	O
is	O
situated	O
120	O
km	O
east	O
of	O
temuco	B-LOC
.	O

he	O
was	O
well	O
respected	O
as	O
a	O
plant	O
breeder	O
and	O
agronomist	B-PER
and	O
developed	O
the	O
sitka	B-LOC
hybrid	O
strawberry	B-PROD
.	O

in	O
the	O
opposite	O
direction	O
moved	O
bronze	O
weapons	O
,	O
furs	O
,	O
ceramic	B-PROD
,	O
and	O
cinnamon	O
bark	O
.	O

this	O
dry	O
meal	O
was	O
put	O
on	O
cake	B-PROD
when	O
fired	O
.	O

following	O
the	O
violence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
transferred	O
to	O
a	O
prison	O
in	O
parma	B-LOC
.	O

he	O
current	O
lives	O
in	O
laketown	B-LOC
,	O
a	O
ranching	O
environment	O
that	O
inspired	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
core	O
ideas	O
in	O
his	O
debut	O
novel	O
.	O

it	O
has	O
been	O
published	O
on	O
a	O
weekly	O
basis	O
since	O
1947	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
owned	O
by	O
yedioth	B-GRP
ahronoth	I-GRP
media	O
group	O
.	O

the	O
song	O
features	O
akon	B-PER
,	O
who	O
also	O
wrote	O
and	O
produced	O
the	O
track	O
with	O
giorgio	B-PER
tuinfort	I-PER
.	O

there	O
were	O
40	O
drivers	O
on	O
the	O
grid	O
;	O
all	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
united	B-LOC
states	I-LOC
of	I-LOC
america	I-LOC
born	O
.	O

the	O
game	O
was	O
inspired	O
by	O
richard	B-PER
adams	I-PER
fantasy	O
novel	O
watership	B-CW
down	I-CW
,	O
and	O
the	O
players	O
were	O
given	O
the	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
on	O
the	O
role	O
of	O
rabbits	O
.	O

the	O
los	B-GRP
angeles	I-GRP
times	I-GRP
called	O
the	O
story	O
quite	O
ordinary	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
film	O
ca	O
nt	O
seem	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
its	O
mind	O
if	O
it	O
's	O
comedy	O
or	O
drama	O
.	O

the	O
race	O
started	O
in	O
milan	B-LOC
and	O
finished	O
in	O
sanremo	B-LOC
.	O

kukla	O
character	O
from	O
kukla,	B-CW
fran	I-CW
and	I-CW
ollie	I-CW

she	O
also	O
worked	O
in	O
theatrical	O
design	O
,	O
including	O
for	O
a	O
production	O
of	O
thieves'	B-CW
carnival	I-CW
by	O
jean	B-PER
anouilh	I-PER
.	O

master	B-CW
of	I-CW
the	I-CW
world	I-CW
(	O
master	O
of	O
the	O
world	O
)	O
,	O
jules	B-PER
verne	I-PER

carried	O
railway	O
over	O
the	O
river	B-LOC
parrett	I-LOC
.	O

after	O
receiving	O
her	O
bachelor	O
of	O
science	O
degree	O
in	O
1964	O
,	O
she	O
studied	O
at	O
the	O
university	B-GRP
of	I-GRP
pittsburgh	I-GRP
for	O
a	O
master	O
's	O
degree	O
in	O
biology	O
.	O

whilst	O
playing	O
for	O
his	O
home	O
town	O
club	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
spotted	O
and	O
offered	O
a	O
contract	O
with	O
the	O
northampton	B-GRP
saints	I-GRP
.	O

he	O
has	O
continued	O
to	O
advise	O
the	O
government	O
's	O
peace	O
team	O
under	O
aung	B-PER
san	I-PER
suu	I-PER
kyi	I-PER
government	O
led	O
administration	O
.	O

vásquez	O
's	O
first	O
assignment	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
province	O
of	O
cagayan	B-LOC
.	O

as	O
of	O
2007	O
he	O
is	O
working	O
on	O
an	O
ice	O
hockey	O
related	O
doctorate	O
and	O
is	O
a	O
member	O
of	O
the	O
disciplinarian	O
committee	O
of	O
the	O
deutsche	B-GRP
eishockey	I-GRP
liga	I-GRP
.	O

it	O
rarely	O
enters	O
plantation	B-CORP
or	O
settlements	O
,	O
preferring	O
the	O
forest	O
.	O

married	O
prince	B-PER
leopold	I-PER
of	I-PER
bavaria	I-PER
(	O
second	O
cousin	O
)	O
in	O
1873	O
;	O
had	O
issue	O
.	O

maslinovo	O
is	O
a	O
village	O
in	O
the	O
municipality	O
of	O
haskovo	B-LOC
,	O
in	O
haskovo	B-LOC
province	I-LOC
,	O
in	O
southern	O
bulgaria	B-LOC
.	O

in	O
these	O
areas	O
,	O
bombing	O
ranges	O
are	O
scoured	O
for	O
salvageable	O
metal	B-PROD
.	O

music	B-CW
video	I-CW
began	O
as	O
promotional	O
films	O
created	O
by	O
a	O
music	O
label	O
's	O
publicity	O
department	O
or	O
an	O
artist	O
's	O
management	O
team	O
.	O

in	O
1934	O
he	O
directed	O
his	O
first	O
picture	O
,	O
the	B-CW
silver	I-CW
streak	I-CW
,	O
which	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
top	O
money	O
makers	O
for	O
rko	B-GRP
pictures	I-GRP
that	O
year	O
.	O

the	O
brand	O
began	O
in	O
1977	O
as	O
an	O
inexpensive	O
alternative	O
to	O
the	O
boutiques	O
of	O
beverly	B-LOC
hills	I-LOC
.	O

the	O
sudden	O
death	O
of	O
the	O
young	O
shunzhi	B-PER
emperor	I-PER
(	O
shunzhi	O
)	O
shocked	O
the	O
whole	O
empire	O
.	O

by	O
1960	O
,	O
rhythm	O
and	O
blues	O
performers	O
on	O
the	O
label	O
included	O
etta	B-PER
james	I-PER
and	O
the	B-GRP
dells	I-GRP
.	O

in	O
1677	O
the	O
church	O
tower	O
collapsed	O
bringing	O
down	O
the	O
west	O
wall	O
with	O
it	O
and	O
damaging	O
the	O
baptismal	B-PROD
font	I-PROD
.	O

the	O
network	O
of	O
fake	O
news	O
websites	O
were	O
used	O
to	O
target	O
policy	O
makers	O
in	O
the	O
united	B-LOC
states	I-LOC
of	I-LOC
america	I-LOC
and	O
the	O
european	B-GRP
union	I-GRP
to	O
act	O
against	O
pakistan	B-LOC
.	O

sólaris	O
,	O
a	O
2011	O
album	O
by	O
daníel	B-PER
bjarnason	I-PER
and	O
ben	B-PER
frost	I-PER

the	O
bar	O
area	O
also	O
features	O
social	O
areas	O
,	O
located	O
next	O
to	O
the	O
exits	O
,	O
and	O
books	O
selected	O
by	O
eslite	B-CORP
bookstore	I-CORP
.	O

in	O
1961	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
magnum	B-CORP
photos	I-CORP
photographers	O
rené	B-PER
burri	I-PER
,	O
elliott	B-PER
erwitt	I-PER
,	O
and	O
burt	B-PER
glinn	I-PER
.	O

to	O
ensure	O
this	O
realism	O
,	O
he	O
collected	O
a	O
wide	O
range	O
of	O
documents	O
about	O
rocket	B-PROD
and	O
space	O
travel	O
with	O
which	O
to	O
conduct	O
research	O
.	O

it	O
was	O
built	O
by	O
kristiania	B-CORP
kommunale	I-CORP
sporveie	I-CORP
(	O
kks	O
)	O
.	O

halpern	O
was	O
for	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
the	O
chairman	O
of	O
the	O
world	B-GRP
ort	I-GRP
.	O

rissa	O
is	O
level	O
headed	O
,	O
a	O
good	O
athlete	O
,	O
and	O
habitually	O
wears	O
cape	B-PROD
.	O

benedict	B-PER
of	I-PER
nursia	I-PER
preaching	O
to	O
his	O
monks	O
(	O
bottom	O
right	O
)	O

each	O
show	O
was	O
a	O
25	O
minute	O
,	O
fast	O
moving	O
mtv	B-CORP
’	O
style	O
programme	O
targeting	O
young	O
people	O
.	O

as	O
the	O
third	O
game	O
in	O
the	O
klonoa	B-CW
handheld	O
series	O
,	O
the	O
game	O
retains	O
many	O
of	O
the	O
gameplay	O
elements	O
of	O
the	O
previous	O
titles	O
,	O
while	O
adding	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
of	O
its	O
own	O
.	O

the	O
premiership	O
changed	O
back	O
to	O
william	B-PER
fox	I-PER
.	O

blackberry	O
devices	O
in	O
the	O
8100	O
and	O
8800	O
series	O
,	O
plus	O
blackberry	B-PROD
curve	I-PROD
8300	O
/	O
8310	O
/	O
8320	O
.	O

from	O
:	O
24	O
/	O
11	O
/	O
1937	O
till	O
:	O
15	O
/	O
05	O
/	O
1938	O
color	O
:	O
liberal	O
text	O
:	O
paul-émile	B-PER
janson	I-PER
fontsize	O
:	O
10	O

this	O
bag	O
supplies	O
its	O
owner	O
with	O
food	O
like	O
,	O
a	O
rice	O
dish	O
seasoned	O
with	O
cinnamon	O
and	O
mastic	O
,	O
sometimes	O
colored	O
with	O
saffron	B-PROD
and	O
prepared	O
stock	O
and	O
tail	O
fat	O
.	O

the	O
2020	O
–	O
21	O
odense	B-GRP
boldklub	I-GRP
season	O
will	O
be	O
the	O
club	O
's	O
132nd	O
season	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
59th	O
appearance	O
in	O
the	O
danish	B-GRP
superliga	I-GRP
.	O

the	O
key	O
element	O
of	O
the	O
toy	O
is	O
the	O
electronic	B-PROD
paper	I-PROD
panel	O
,	O
filled	O
with	O
a	O
thick	O
,	O
opaque	O
white	O
liquid	O
containing	O
tiny	O
dark	O
magnet	B-PROD
.	O

schifrin	O
made	O
a	O
cameo	O
appearance	O
in	O
red	B-CW
dragon	I-CW
as	O
an	O
orchestra	O
conductor	O
.	O

three	O
major	O
railways	O
,	O
the	O
shanghai–kunming	B-LOC
railway	I-LOC
,	O
the	O
jiaozuo–liuzhou	B-LOC
railway	I-LOC
,	O
and	O
the	O
chongqing–huaihua	B-LOC
railway	I-LOC
,	O
intersect	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
.	O

#	O
say	B-CW
my	I-CW
name	I-CW
destiny's	B-GRP
child	I-GRP
(	O
mistakenly	O
credited	O
as	O
say	O
your	O
name	O
)	O

karimi	O
joined	O
paykan	B-GRP
f.c.	I-GRP
in	O
winter	O
2013	O
.	O

he	O
was	O
awarded	O
the	O
order	B-GRP
of	I-GRP
polonia	I-GRP
restituta	I-GRP
.	O

sr	O
26	O
also	O
passes	O
through	O
graysville	B-LOC
and	O
woodsfield	B-LOC
.	O

seethalakshmi	O
(	O
latha	B-PER
)	O
is	O
the	O
owner	O
of	O
a	O
clothing	O
company	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
haughty	O
and	O
strict	O
woman	O
.	O

the	O
plant	O
also	O
manufactures	O
the	O
kia	B-PROD
carnival	I-PROD
exclusively	O
for	O
the	O
domestic	O
market	O
.	O

the	O
following	O
year	O
,	O
the	O
world	O
's	O
longest	O
rope	O
bridge	O
,	O
now	O
even	O
listed	O
in	O
the	O
guinness	B-CW
world	I-CW
records	I-CW
,	O
was	O
opened	O
.	O

in	O
1979	O
the	O
conservative	B-GRP
party	I-GRP
government	O
led	O
by	O
margaret	B-PER
thatcher	I-PER
began	O
privatising	O
the	O
nationalised	O
industries	O
.	O

they	O
are	O
the	O
company	O
's	O
first	O
scooter	O
since	O
the	O
bmw	B-PROD
c1	I-PROD
,	O
which	O
was	O
manufactured	O
by	O
bertone	B-CORP
.	O

self	O
portrait	O
is	O
a	O
painting	O
by	O
the	O
finland	B-LOC
artist	O
vilho	B-PER
lampi	I-PER
(	O
1898	O
–	O
1936	O
)	O
from	O
1933	O
.	O

she	O
is	O
the	O
co	O
founder	O
of	O
the	O
mobile	O
gaming	O
company	O
kabam	B-CORP
.	O

the	O
majority	O
of	O
money	O
turnover	O
consisted	O
of	O
small	O
copper	B-PROD
coins	O
.	O

an	O
alternate	O
meeting	O
was	O
held	O
instead	O
despite	O
pressure	O
from	O
australia	B-LOC
and	O
new	B-LOC
zealand	I-LOC
.	O

she	O
turned	O
down	O
a	O
co	O
starring	O
role	O
in	O
body	B-CW
heat	I-CW
due	O
to	O
the	O
overtly	O
sexual	O
nature	O
of	O
the	O
film	O
.	O

the	O
music	O
of	O
the	O
film	O
was	O
composed	O
by	O
mani	B-PER
sharma	I-PER
.	O

in	O
2003	O
it	O
was	O
registered	O
as	O
a	O
nonprofit	B-GRP
organization	I-GRP
.	O

two	O
examples	O
of	O
people	O
forced	O
to	O
leave	O
were	O
the	O
families	O
of	O
béla	B-PER
hamvas	I-PER
and	O
albert	B-PER
szent-györgyi	I-PER
.	O

hozier	B-CW
by	O
hozier	B-PER
was	O
the	O
only	O
album	O
from	O
2014	O
to	O
reach	O
its	O
peak	O
in	O
2015	O
.	O

cable	O
is	O
playable	O
in	O
marvel:	B-CW
future	I-CW
fight	I-CW
.	O

di	O
thrift	O
stores	O
are	O
similar	O
to	O
the	O
well	O
known	O
goodwill	B-GRP
industries	I-GRP
.	O

needham	O
was	O
admitted	O
to	O
the	O
bar	O
in	O
1821	O
and	O
established	O
a	O
practice	O
in	O
bristol	B-LOC
.	O

it	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
indirect	O
presidential	O
election	O
in	O
taiwan	B-LOC
.	O

it	O
is	O
also	O
referred	O
to	O
as	O
an	O
icebox	B-PROD
cake	I-PROD
.	O

it	O
was	O
powered	O
by	O
an	O
argus	B-PROD
as	I-PROD
10	I-PROD
,	O
of	O
.	O

frisch	O
earned	O
a	O
ph	O
.	O
d	O
.	O
in	O
1967	O
from	O
the	O
university	B-GRP
of	I-GRP
paris	I-GRP
,	O
and	O
since	O
then	O
he	O
has	O
worked	O
at	O
the	O
national	B-GRP
center	I-GRP
for	I-GRP
scientific	I-GRP
research	I-GRP
(	O
cnrs	O
)	O
.	O

1977	O
:	O
cabretta	B-CW
(	O
in	O
europe	O
)	O
;	O
cabretta	B-CW
(	O
in	O
the	O
u.s.	O
)	O
(	O
capitol	B-CORP
records	I-CORP
)	O

hartsop	O
is	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
civil	B-LOC
parish	I-LOC
of	O
patterdale	B-LOC
.	O

it	O
lies	O
in	O
the	O
hydrographic	O
basin	O
of	O
the	O
south	B-LOC
saskatchewan	I-LOC
river	I-LOC
and	O
has	O
a	O
drainage	O
area	O
of	O
.	O

in	O
1919	O
comenius	B-GRP
university	I-GRP
in	I-GRP
bratislava	I-GRP
was	O
founded	O
by	O
an	O
act	O
of	O
parliament	O
in	O
bratislava	B-LOC
,	O
czechoslovakia	B-LOC
,	O
now	O
in	O
slovakia	B-LOC
.	O

helen	B-PER
reddy	I-PER
recorded	O
the	O
song	O
for	O
all	B-CW
this	I-CW
and	I-CW
world	I-CW
war	I-CW
ii	I-CW
,	O
a	O
1976	O
film	O
in	O
which	O
wartime	O
newsreel	O
was	O
set	O
to	O
a	O
soundtrack	O
of	O
lennon	O
–	O
mccartney	O
songs	O
.	O

in	O
the	O
fourth	O
round	O
he	O
lost	O
in	O
straight	O
sets	O
to	O
ham	B-PER
richardson	I-PER
.	O

čermná	O
is	O
a	O
village	O
in	O
the	O
czech	B-LOC
republic	I-LOC
.	O

ue	B-GRP
engordany	I-GRP
were	O
the	O
defending	O
champions	O
after	O
winning	O
the	O
final	O
over	O
fc	B-GRP
santa	I-GRP
coloma	I-GRP
by	O
a	O
score	O
of	O
2	O
–	O
0	O
.	O

a	B-CW
moment	I-CW
like	I-CW
this	I-CW
,	O
representing	O
the	O
oldest	O
material	O
on	O
the	O
compilation	O
,	O
is	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
non	O
album	O
single	O
before	B-CW
your	I-CW
love	I-CW
/	O
a	O
moment	O
like	O
this	O
in	O
2002	O
.	O

selected	O
students	O
were	O
given	O
a	O
laptop	O
(	O
manufactured	O
by	O
haier	B-CORP
)	O
and	O
a	O
3g	O
evo	O
device	O
.	O

warner	B-GRP
bros.	I-GRP
and	O
atlantic	B-CORP
records	I-CORP
have	O
also	O
used	O
his	O
art	O
.	O

the	B-CW
citadel	I-CW
–	O
as	O
co	O
writer	O

he	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
the	O
actress	O
freda	B-PER
jackson	I-PER
to	O
whom	O
he	O
was	O
devoted	O
and	O
committed	O
.	O

he	O
was	O
signed	O
by	O
the	O
tennessee	B-GRP
titans	I-GRP
as	O
an	O
undrafted	O
free	O
agent	O
in	O
2015	O
.	O

both	O
sites	O
are	O
owned	O
by	O
hammerson	B-CORP
.	O

both	O
the	O
smithsonian	B-CORP
institution	I-CORP
and	O
ralph	B-PER
stanley	I-PER
tried	O
without	O
success	O
to	O
get	O
her	O
back	O
onstage	O
.	O

the	O
first	O
known	O
recipe	O
of	O
a	O
tomato	B-PROD
sauce	I-PROD
with	O
pasta	O
is	O
depicted	O
in	O
this	O
book	O
.	O

mechau	O
is	O
a	O
village	O
and	O
a	O
former	O
municipality	O
in	O
the	O
district	O
altmarkkreis	B-LOC
salzwedel	I-LOC
,	O
in	O
saxony-anhalt	B-LOC
,	O
germany	B-LOC
.	O

the	O
term	O
real	O
time	O
strategy	O
was	O
coined	O
by	O
brett	B-PER
sperry	I-PER
to	O
market	O
dune	B-CW
ii	I-CW
in	O
the	O
early	O
1990s	O
.	O

better	B-CORP
place	I-CORP
,	O
a	O
defunct	O
electric	O
car	O
company	O

she	O
defeated	O
jessica	B-PER
moore	I-PER
and	O
alexandra	B-PER
panova	I-PER
but	O
was	O
defeated	O
by	O
anastasia	B-PER
pivovarova	I-PER
in	O
the	O
third	O
qualifying	O
round	O
.	O

the	B-CW
sicilian	I-CW
,	O
directed	O
by	O
michael	B-PER
cimino	I-PER
,	O
starring	O
christopher	B-PER
lambert	I-PER

bangladesh	O
–	O
kyrgyzstan	O
relations	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
bilateral	O
(	O
two	O
way	O
)	O
relations	O
between	O
bangladesh	B-LOC
and	O
kyrgyzstan	B-LOC
.	O

his	O
approach	O
was	O
to	O
use	O
a	O
balloon	O
width	O
bicycle	B-PROD
tire	I-PROD
of	O
about	O
2.25	O
(	O
57	O
mm	O
)	O
on	O
a	O
20	O
(	O
500	O
mm	O
)	O
rim	O
,	O
giving	O
a	O
wheel	O
of	O
approximately	O
24	O
(	O
600	O
mm	O
)	O
in	O
diameter	O
.	O

crusade	O
has	O
a	O
rating	O
of	O
3.44	O
stars	O
on	O
goodreads	B-CORP
.	O

the	O
historical	O
drama	O
film	O
the	B-CW
hunchback	I-CW
of	I-CW
notre	I-CW
dame	I-CW
was	O
released	O
.	O

pieces	O
at	O
the	O
start	O
of	O
a	O
game	O
and	O
an	O
analog	O
chess	B-PROD
clock	I-PROD

adaptation	O
of	O
seinen	B-CW
series	O
by	O
kenichi	B-PER
sonoda	I-PER
.	O

2005	O
–	O
2011	O
:	O
family	B-CW
guy	I-CW
9	O
episodes	O

he	O
studied	O
law	O
at	O
cairo	B-GRP
university	I-GRP
.	O

her	O
engines	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
were	O
completed	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
installed	O
in	O
the	O
screw	O
steamboat	B-PROD
.	O

replaced	O
by	O
t	B-LOC
third	I-LOC
street	I-LOC
and	O
9x	O
bayshore	O
express	O
(	O
now	O
8	O
bayshore	O
)	O

after	O
a	O
series	O
of	O
civil	O
jobs	O
he	O
settled	O
in	O
kristiansand	B-LOC
in	O
1892	O
as	O
a	O
postmaster	O
.	O

wagner	O
retired	O
to	O
crozet	B-LOC
,	O
following	O
the	O
2010	O
season	O
.	O

he	O
specialized	O
in	O
outdoor	O
cinematography	O
often	O
on	O
western	B-CW
and	O
action	O
adventure	O
films	O
.	O

she	O
worked	O
for	O
many	O
years	O
in	O
the	O
drama	O
department	O
of	O
radio	B-CORP
belgrade	I-CORP
,	O
writing	O
and	O
producing	O
numerous	O
radio	O
plays	O
during	O
that	O
time	O
.	O

south	B-CORP
china	I-CORP
morning	I-CORP
post	I-CORP
,	O
however	O
,	O
stated	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
thought	O
provoking	O
sentimental	B-CW
ballad	I-CW
.	O

briarhills	O
is	O
a	O
subdivision	O
in	O
western	O
houston	B-LOC
,	O
texas	B-LOC
.	O

khosrau	O
finally	O
captured	O
it	O
in	O
573	O
;	O
its	O
fall	O
was	O
said	O
to	O
have	O
caused	O
justin	B-PER
ii	I-PER
to	O
go	O
insane	O
.	O

he	O
also	O
became	O
a	O
harsh	O
critic	O
of	O
the	O
jewish	B-GRP
anti-fascist	I-GRP
committee	I-GRP
in	O
the	O
post	O
war	O
years	O
.	O

the	O
poem	O
also	O
inspired	O
symphonic	B-CW
poem	I-CW
by	O
edward	B-PER
macdowell	I-PER
and	O
dorothy	B-PER
howell	I-PER
.	O

yaroslavl	B-LOC
,	O
komatsu	B-CORP
limited	I-CORP
established	O
in	O
2010	O
,	O
produces	O
rigid	O
dump	O
trucks	O
.	O

these	O
are	O
all	O
multi	O
storey	O
brick	O
apartment	O
buildings	O
,	O
which	O
effectively	O
reflect	O
the	O
architectural	O
style	O
and	O
character	O
of	O
the	O
cityscape	B-CW
in	O
the	O
latter	O
half	O
of	O
the	O
19th	O
century	O
.	O

in	O
1949	O
he	O
graduated	O
in	O
pharmacy	O
from	O
jagiellonian	B-GRP
university	I-GRP
.	O

gunfire	O
from	O
the	O
van	O
erupted	O
,	O
hitting	O
the	O
volkswagen	B-PROD
beetle	I-PROD
gas	O
tank	O
.	O

turner	B-CORP
entertainment	I-CORP
supported	O
the	O
show	O
through	O
a	O
massive	O
marketing	O
campaign	O
with	O
thirty	O
three	O
licensees	O
.	O

they	O
aimed	O
to	O
improve	O
on	O
the	O
series	O
by	O
giving	O
the	O
game	O
a	O
coherent	O
tone	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
films	O
such	O
as	O
hot	B-CW
fuzz	I-CW
and	O
the	O
game	O
's	O
signature	O
sex	B-PROD
toy	I-PROD
bat	O
.	O

totaling	O
25	O
tracks	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
charlie	O
brown	O
jr	O
.	O
s	O
longest	O
album	O
;	O
in	O
an	O
interview	O
,	O
vocalist	O
chorão	B-PER
explained	O
that	O
preço	O
curto	O
.	O
.	O
.	O

the	O
bankura	O
–	O
masagram	O
line	O
is	O
a	O
broad	O
gauge	O
rail	O
line	O
connecting	O
bankura	B-LOC
and	O
masagram	B-LOC
.	O

animation	O
:	O
richard	B-PER
thompson	I-PER
,	O
ken	B-PER
harris	I-PER
,	O
don	B-PER
towsley	I-PER
,	O
tom	B-PER
ray	I-PER
&	O
phil	B-PER
roman	I-PER

in	O
home	B-CW
sweet	I-CW
home	I-CW
,	O
she	O
played	O
a	O
hardened	O
nurse	O
who	O
is	O
changed	O
by	O
a	O
love	O
affair	O
with	O
a	O
social	O
worker	O
(	O
jacques	B-PER
perrin	I-PER
)	O
.	O

november	O
6	O
:	O
michael	B-PER
howard	I-PER
replaces	O
iain	B-PER
duncan	I-PER
smith	I-PER
as	O
leader	O
of	O
the	O
conservative	B-GRP
party	I-GRP
in	O
the	O
united	B-LOC
kingdom	I-LOC

he	O
advanced	O
,	O
attacked	O
the	O
enemy	O
's	O
infantry	O
with	O
the	O
lance	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
retired	O
while	O
the	O
enemy	O
swarmed	O
out	O
of	O
hidden	O
ground	O
where	O
royal	B-GRP
artillery	I-GRP
guns	O
could	O
attack	O
them	O
.	O

the	O
club	O
has	O
a	O
local	O
rival	O
,	O
ferenc	B-GRP
puskás	I-GRP
football	I-GRP
academy	I-GRP
,	O
based	O
in	O
felcsút	B-LOC
,	O
fejér	B-LOC
county	I-LOC
,	O
but	O
the	O
rivalry	O
is	O
relatively	O
tame	O
.	O

june	O
20	O
–	O
alexis	B-PER
neiers	I-PER
,	O
television	O
personality	O
and	O
model	O

a	O
solar	B-PROD
car	I-PROD
uses	O
less	O
power	O
than	O
a	O
toaster	O
,	O
but	O
can	O
travel	O
continuously	O
at	O
55	O
mph	O
using	O
energy	O
stored	O
in	O
batteries	O
,	O
charged	O
only	O
from	O
the	O
car	O
's	O
solar	O
panels	O
.	O

some	O
airlines	O
,	O
like	O
air	B-CORP
afrique	I-CORP
,	O
were	O
jointly	O
sponsored	O
by	O
multiple	O
governments	O
.	O

bryan	B-PER
herta	I-PER
struck	O
a	O
stray	O
tire	B-PROD
from	O
the	O
accident	O
,	O
ending	O
his	O
day	O
as	O
well	O
.	O

he	O
started	O
and	O
ended	O
his	O
16	O
year	O
professional	O
career	O
with	O
real	B-GRP
unión	I-GRP
,	O
but	O
played	O
mainly	O
for	O
levante	B-GRP
ud	I-GRP
(	O
eight	O
seasons	O
and	O
226	O
official	O
matches	O
,	O
61	O
in	O
laliga	B-CORP
)	O
.	O

the	O
arcade	O
shoot	O
em	O
up	O
xevious	B-CW
(	O
from	O
namco	B-CORP
1983	O
,	O
designed	O
by	O
masanobu	B-PER
endō	I-PER
)	O
were	O
also	O
deeply	O
inspired	O
on	O
ancient	O
astronaut	O
theories	O
.	O

m-5	B-PROD
–	O
single	O
engined	O
training	O
or	O
reconnaissance	O
flying	O
boat	O

he	O
attended	O
the	O
american	B-GRP
film	I-GRP
institute	I-GRP
,	O
and	O
started	O
his	O
professional	O
career	O
as	O
a	O
film	O
editor	O
for	O
roger	B-PER
corman	I-PER
.	O

problems	O
with	O
his	O
suzuki	B-PROD
gsx-r1000	I-PROD
saw	O
him	O
retire	O
in	O
both	O
races	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
machine	O
featured	O
.	O

it	O
is	O
estimated	O
that	O
a	O
single	O
garment	O
factory	O
can	O
create	O
up	O
to	O
60,000	O
pounds	O
(	O
27	O
metric	O
tons	O
)	O
of	O
textile	B-PROD
waste	O
,	O
which	O
normally	O
goes	O
to	O
landfills	O
.	O

she	O
studied	O
at	O
howard	B-GRP
university	I-GRP
with	O
the	O
plan	O
to	O
become	O
a	O
teacher	O
.	O

for	O
financial	O
services	O
to	O
the	O
poor	O
,	O
see	O
microfinance	B-PROD
.	O

payne	O
is	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
former	O
national	B-CORP
basketball	I-CORP
association	I-CORP
player	O
mitchell	B-PER
wiggins	I-PER
.	O

his	O
success	O
in	O
the	O
public	O
sphere	O
led	O
to	O
his	O
appointment	O
by	O
pius	B-PER
ix	I-PER
to	O
the	O
position	O
of	O
second	O
bishop	O
of	O
portland	B-LOC
.	O

syntagma	B-CW
musicum	I-CW
,	O
a	O
17th	O
century	O
work	O
of	O
organology	O
by	O
michael	B-PER
praetorius	I-PER

with	O
flight	O
operations	O
based	O
at	O
stuttgart	B-LOC
airport	I-LOC
,	O
it	O
operated	O
scheduled	O
passenger	O
flights	O
under	O
the	O
lufthansa	B-CORP
regional	I-CORP
brand	O
.	O

moses	O
in	O
dogville	B-CW
2003	O
winner	O

in	O
a	O
džuboks	B-CW
review	O
,	O
maksa	B-PER
ćatović	I-PER
wrote	O
:	O

the	O
drainage	O
within	O
the	O
state	O
of	O
hawaii	B-LOC
.	O

take	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
limits	O
of	O
the	O
sun	O
kuwait	B-LOC
1997	O

:	O
the	O
nissan	B-PROD
leaf	I-PROD
,	O
audi	B-PROD
a8	I-PROD
,	O
and	O
bmw	B-PROD
5	I-PROD
series	I-PROD
were	O
the	O
top	O
three	O
finalists	O
.	O

it	O
is	O
found	O
in	O
peru	B-LOC
and	O
brazil	B-LOC
.	O

along	O
with	O
husband	O
antony	B-PER
ressler	I-PER
,	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
part	O
owner	O
of	O
the	O
atlanta	B-GRP
hawks	I-GRP
of	O
the	O
national	B-CORP
basketball	I-CORP
association	I-CORP
.	O

he	O
remembered	O
once	O
hearing	O
the	O
song	O
on	O
the	O
radio	O
and	O
feeling	O
like	O
the	O
boy	O
from	O
swindon	B-LOC
made	O
good	O
.	O

however	O
,	O
the	O
result	O
showed	O
a	O
50	O
percent	O
success	O
rate	O
,	O
since	O
agatha	B-PER
barbara	I-PER
was	O
elected	O
.	O

from	O
1954	O
until	O
2007	O
,	O
the	O
town	O
was	O
the	O
home	O
to	O
the	O
exclusive	O
sports	O
car	O
manufacturer	O
aston	B-CORP
martin	I-CORP
lagonda	I-CORP
.	O

over	O
12	O
seasons	O
,	O
he	O
amassed	O
laliga	B-CORP
totals	O
of	O
244	O
matches	O
and	O
18	O
goals	O
,	O
also	O
representing	O
in	O
the	O
competition	O
real	B-GRP
valladolid	I-GRP
and	O
cádiz	B-GRP
c.f.	I-GRP
.	O

empowerment	B-GRP
:	O
to	O
strengthen	O
capacity	O
building	O
by	O
making	O
all	O
relevant	O
actors	O
,	O
including	O
beneficiaries	O
,	O
work	O
together	O
on	O
an	O
equal	O
footing	O
.	O

upgrade	O
for	O
a	O
key	O
stretch	O
of	O
bulgaria	B-LOC
railway	O
infrastructure	O
completed	O
in	O
2010	O

in	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
commercial	O
versions	O
of	O
the	O
food	O
,	O
chocolate	B-PROD
is	O
added	O
to	O
it	O
.	O

a	O
number	O
of	O
remixes	O
were	O
commissioned	O
by	O
jive	B-CORP
records	I-CORP
to	O
accompany	O
the	O
release	O
.	O

the	O
video	O
begins	O
with	O
zendaya	B-PER
and	O
other	O
kids	O
come	O
into	O
school	O
where	O
several	O
people	O
crowded	O
the	O
hallways	O
and	O
others	O
walk	O
into	O
the	O
classroom	O
.	O

some	O
of	O
its	O
workers	O
founded	O
pyro	B-CORP
studios	I-CORP
in	O
1998	O
.	O

communication	O
means	O
the	O
creator	O
has	O
accepted	O
responsibility	O
for	O
an	O
intense	O
stew	O
of	O
elements	O
(	O
a	O
paella	B-PROD
?	O
)	O
which	O
now	O
includes	O
nutrition	O
.	O

#	O
the	B-CW
slider	I-CW
mike	B-PER
patton	I-PER
as	O
fantômas	B-GRP
1	O
:	O
51	O

detroit	B-CORP
electric	I-CORP
,	O
an	O
early	O
automobile	O
manufacturer	O

they	O
have	O
also	O
appeared	O
in	O
tiny	B-CW
toon	I-CW
adventures	I-CW
.	O

when	O
the	O
grain	O
is	O
mill	B-LOC
the	O
smut	O
balls	O
emit	O
a	O
fishy	O
odor	O
that	O
lowers	O
the	O
quality	O
of	O
the	O
wheat	B-PROD
flour	I-PROD
.	O

the	O
band	O
is	O
then	O
resurrected	O
by	O
a	O
member	O
playing	O
when	B-CW
the	I-CW
saints	I-CW
go	I-CW
marching	I-CW
in	I-CW
.	O

scientific	B-CORP
atlanta	I-CORP
digital	O
cable	O
boxes	O
were	O
provided	O
to	O
all	O
customers	O
in	O
1999	O
and	O
2000	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
the	O
company	O
tried	O
to	O
implement	O
tiered	O
service	O
packages	O
.	O

in	O
1929	O
,	O
while	O
still	O
a	O
graduate	O
student	O
at	O
cornell	B-GRP
university	I-GRP
,	O
he	O
travelled	O
on	O
an	O
expedition	O
to	O
madagascar	B-LOC
as	O
collector	O
of	O
birds	O
.	O

the	O
dallas	B-GRP
cowboys	I-GRP
had	O
also	O
put	O
in	O
a	O
claim	O
for	O
him	O
.	O

investigations	O
later	O
established	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
visited	O
york	B-LOC
,	O
bradford	B-LOC
and	O
bridlington	B-LOC
,	O
but	O
no	O
indication	O
of	O
why	O
or	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
there	O
.	O

apple	B-CORP
inc.	I-CORP
sued	O
to	O
prevent	O
other	O
software	O
companies	O
from	O
offering	O
graphical	O
user	O
interfaces	O
similar	O
to	O
its	O
own	O
.	O

during	O
the	O
late	O
1980s	O
and	O
early	O
1990s	O
,	O
ford	B-CORP
motor	I-CORP
company	I-CORP
played	O
the	O
song	O
in	O
advertisements	O
for	O
its	O
ford	B-PROD
mustang	I-PROD
pony	B-PROD
car	I-PROD
.	O

during	O
this	O
cruise	O
,	O
she	O
made	O
one	O
trip	O
to	O
haiti	B-LOC
as	O
tension	O
there	O
rose	O
.	O

visitors	O
and	O
locals	O
can	O
go	O
around	O
the	O
city	O
by	O
just	O
hailing	O
a	O
sikad	O
sikad	O
or	O
motorboat	O
,	O
jeepney	B-PROD
or	O
motorcycles	O
to	O
the	O
outlying	O
barangays	O
.	O

the	O
route	O
would	O
later	O
be	O
truncated	O
to	O
brenda	B-LOC
.	O

in	O
the	O
chancel	O
is	O
a	O
double	O
piscina	B-PROD
.	O

the	O
project	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
constructed	O
by	O
areva	B-CORP
using	O
superheated	O
solar	O
steam	O
technology	O
.	O

he	O
partnered	O
with	O
fanny	B-PER
crosby	I-PER
and	O
published	O
over	O
twenty	O
of	O
her	O
hymns	O
in	O
his	O
hymnals	O
.	O

knapp	O
appeared	O
as	O
the	O
main	O
villain	O
,	O
opposite	O
bruce	B-PER
willis	I-PER
,	O
in	O
eli	B-PER
roth	I-PER
death	B-CW
wish	I-CW
of	O
death	B-CW
wish	I-CW
.	O

it	O
is	O
located	O
7	O
km	O
from	O
sabadell	B-LOC
and	O
11	O
km	O
from	O
terrassa	B-LOC
,	O
the	O
comarca	O
's	O
two	O
capitals	O
.	O

he	O
practiced	O
at	O
o'melveny	B-CORP
&	I-CORP
myers	I-CORP
from	O
1993	O
to	O
2006	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
served	O
as	O
co	O
chair	O
of	O
the	O
healthcare	O
and	O
environmental	O
law	O
practice	O
groups	O
.	O

in	O
1948	O
he	O
played	O
in	O
a	O
trio	O
with	O
dave	B-PER
brubeck	I-PER
,	O
and	O
in	O
1949	O
with	O
paul	B-PER
desmond	I-PER
.	O

bellwether	B-CW
:	O
novel	O
:	O
1998	O

the	O
company	O
had	O
a	O
debt	O
annual	O
revenue	O
ratio	O
of	O
44	O
%	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
higher	O
than	O
that	O
of	O
its	O
competitors	O
cbre	B-CORP
group	I-CORP
,	O
jones	B-CORP
lang	I-CORP
lasalle	I-CORP
and	O
zillow	B-CORP
.	O

johnny	B-CW
the	I-CW
homicidal	I-CW
maniac	I-CW
#	O
1	O
–	O
7	O
(	O
by	O
jhonen	B-PER
vasquez	I-PER
,	O
1995	O
–	O
1997	O
)	O

an	O
inswinger	O
is	O
bowled	O
by	O
holding	O
the	O
cricket	B-PROD
ball	I-PROD
with	O
the	O
seam	O
vertical	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
two	O
fingers	O
slightly	O
across	O
the	O
seam	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
angled	O
a	O
little	O
to	O
the	O
leg	O
side	O
.	O

will	B-PER
smith	I-PER
and	O
jada	B-PER
pinkett	I-PER
smith	I-PER
were	O
the	O
executive	O
producers	O
for	O
this	O
production	O
.	O

this	O
marine	O
species	O
occurs	O
off	O
indonesia	B-LOC
.	O

he	O
has	O
played	O
in	O
major	B-CORP
league	I-CORP
baseball	I-CORP
(	O
mlb	O
)	O
with	O
the	O
washington	B-GRP
nationals	I-GRP
.	O

in	O
2004	O
,	O
readers	O
of	O
retro	B-CW
gamer	I-CW
voted	O
it	O
as	O
the	O
29th	O
top	O
retro	O
game	O
.	O

in	O
2013	O
it	O
was	O
rated	O
the	O
best	O
place	O
to	O
live	O
in	O
a	O
survey	O
by	O
the	B-GRP
sunday	I-GRP
times	I-GRP
.	O

ableton	B-CORP
addressed	O
some	O
confusion	O
in	O
an	O
article	O
:	O

during	O
the	O
1960s	O
he	O
joined	O
a	O
band	O
led	O
by	O
clarinetist	O
ove	B-PER
lind	I-PER
in	O
the	O
swing	O
style	O
of	O
benny	B-PER
goodman	I-PER
.	O

the	O
organisation	O
supports	O
microfinance	B-PROD
programmes	O
with	O
a	O
strong	O
social	O
orientation	O
,	O
which	O
target	O
thousands	O
of	O
very	O
deprived	O
women	O
and	O
men	O
.	O

derek	B-PER
kennard	I-PER
,	O
former	O
guard	O
and	O
center	O
for	O
the	O
national	B-CORP
football	I-CORP
league	I-CORP
and	O
united	B-GRP
states	I-GRP
football	I-GRP
league	I-GRP
.	O

the	O
duo	O
was	O
subsequently	O
dropped	O
from	O
its	O
syndicator	O
,	O
westwood	B-CORP
one	I-CORP
,	O
due	O
to	O
the	O
loss	O
of	O
outlets	O
carrying	O
the	O
show	O
.	O

only	O
mount	B-LOC
davidson	I-LOC
is	O
higher	O
within	O
the	O
city	O
.	O

mucheong	O
–	O
radish	O
greens	O
,	O
dried	O
to	O
make	O
siraegi	B-PROD
or	O
used	O
fresh	O
in	O
cooking	O
.	O

primatt	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
london	B-LOC
,	O
in	O
1734	O
.	O

they	O
were	O
apparently	O
unaware	O
that	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
not	O
empty	O
but	O
contained	O
a	O
painting	O
by	O
lucian	B-PER
freud	I-PER
worth	O
about	O
$	O
157,000	O
.	O

for	O
five	O
voices	O
(	O
coburg	O
:	O
kaspar	O
bertsch	O
)	O
,	O
a	O
epithalamium	B-CW

#	O
i	B-CW
only	I-CW
have	I-CW
eyes	I-CW
for	I-CW
you	I-CW
(	O
al	B-PER
dubin	I-PER
,	O
harry	B-PER
warren	I-PER
)	O
–	O
2	O
:	O
52	O

banshee	B-CW
(	O
2013	O
2016	O
)	O
10	O
episodes	O
(	O
credited	O
as	O
o.c.	O
madsen	O
)	O

it	O
is	O
4	O
km	O
northwest	O
of	O
zakynthos	B-LOC
.	O

she	O
joined	O
cnn	B-CORP
as	O
a	O
political	O
analyst	O
in	O
2017	O
.	O

it	O
is	O
a	O
sister	O
company	O
of	O
latam	B-CORP
cargo	I-CORP
chile	I-CORP
and	O
latam	B-CORP
cargo	I-CORP
colombia	I-CORP
.	O

zone	O
tails	O
sometimes	O
wander	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
normal	O
range	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bird	O
was	O
once	O
recorded	O
in	O
nova	B-LOC
scotia	I-LOC
.	O

rotimatic	O
uses	O
machine	O
learning	O
to	O
make	O
bread	O
and	O
takes	O
about	O
a	O
minute	O
to	O
make	O
one	O
roti	B-PROD
.	O

in	O
the	O
early	O
years	O
of	O
the	O
centre	O
's	O
existence	O
,	O
the	O
site	O
was	O
known	O
as	O
the	O
broadway	O
shopping	O
centre	O
;	O
its	O
owners	O
included	O
aviva	B-CORP
.	O

1975	O
–	O
come	B-CW
taste	I-CW
the	I-CW
band	I-CW
(	O
co	O
producer	O
,	O
engineer	O
,	O
mixing	O
)	O

this	O
year	O
's	O
team	O
finished	O
in	O
second	O
place	O
for	O
progressive	O
fk	B-GRP
slovan	I-GRP
duslo	I-GRP
šaľa	I-GRP
.	O

superscripts	O
denote	O
lead	O
singers	O
for	O
each	O
track	O
:	O
(	O
a	O
)	O
scherrie	B-PER
payne	I-PER
,	O
(	O
b	O
)	O
mary	B-PER
wilson	I-PER
.	O

the	O
following	O
day	O
oft	O
injured	O
veteran	O
midfielder	O
carl	B-PER
robinson	I-PER
retired	O
and	O
joined	O
the	O
coaching	O
staff	O
of	O
vancouver	B-GRP
whitecaps	I-GRP
fc	I-GRP
.	O

i	B-CW
love	I-CW
you	I-CW
because	I-CW
is	O
a	O
song	O
by	O
leon	B-PER
payne	I-PER
,	O
original	O
probably	O
1949	O
,	O
capitol	O
;	O
eddie	B-PER
fisher	I-PER
(	O
1950	O
,	O
rca	O
victor	O
)	O

the	O
following	O
airline	B-CORP
offer	O
scheduled	O
passenger	O
service	O
at	O
this	O
airport	O
:	O

ro	O
,	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
in	O
parole	O
,	O
played	O
by	O
melonie	B-PER
diaz	I-PER
,	O
goes	O
to	O
a	O
speed	O
dating	O
bar	O
trying	O
to	O
rebuild	O
his	O
life	O
after	O
prison	O
.	O

it	O
is	O
found	O
in	O
benin	B-LOC
,	O
ivory	B-LOC
coast	I-LOC
,	O
ghana	B-LOC
,	O
guinea	B-LOC
,	O
liberia	B-LOC
,	O
senegal	B-LOC
,	O
sierra	B-LOC
leone	I-LOC
,	O
and	O
togo	B-LOC
.	O

he	O
replaced	O
álvaro	B-PER
morata	I-PER
after	O
93	O
minutes	O
in	O
a	O
2	O
–	O
0	O
away	O
win	O
.	O

benicarló	O
is	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
taula	B-GRP
del	I-GRP
sénia	I-GRP
free	O
association	O
of	O
municipalities	O
.	O

he	O
briefly	O
attended	O
the	O
the	B-GRP
wharton	I-GRP
school	I-GRP
before	O
transferring	O
to	O
harvard	B-GRP
university	I-GRP
.	O

it	O
was	O
designed	O
by	O
kohn	B-CORP
pedersen	I-CORP
fox	I-CORP
.	O

ramrod	O
,	O
1943	O
—	O
ramrod	B-CW
,	O
1947	O

in	O
the	O
autumn	O
of	O
1950	O
the	O
model	O
returned	O
with	O
a	O
new	O
front	O
,	O
similar	O
to	O
the	O
front	O
of	O
the	O
volvo	B-PROD
pv444/544	I-PROD
and	O
the	O
small	O
lorry	O
volvo	B-PROD
l340	I-PROD
.	O

bernardini	B-CORP
,	O
safe	O
manufacturer	O
which	O
operated	O
from	O
1912	O
to	O
1992	O

leyland	O
was	O
the	O
manager	O
of	O
the	O
pittsburgh	B-GRP
pirates	I-GRP
from	O
1986	O
to	O
1996	O
.	O

the	O
mitsubishi	B-PROD
rvr	I-PROD
replaced	O
the	O
van	O
/	O
wagon	O
in	O
1992	O
.	O

he	O
semi	O
retired	O
to	O
portugal	B-LOC
in	O
2016	O
.	O

round	O
10	O
:	O
ben	B-PER
hunt	I-PER
played	O
his	O
150th	O
career	O
game	O
.	O

the	O
entire	O
collection	O
now	O
rests	O
in	O
the	O
library	O
of	O
the	O
university	B-GRP
of	I-GRP
amsterdam	I-GRP
.	O

the	O
tempting	O
target	O
of	O
a	O
realistic	O
papier-mâché	B-PROD
head	O
was	O
raised	O
above	O
the	O
parapet	O
on	O
a	O
stick	O
running	O
in	O
a	O
groove	O
on	O
a	O
fixed	O
board	O
.	O

it	O
was	O
originally	O
published	O
by	O
little,	B-CORP
brown	I-CORP
and	I-CORP
company	I-CORP
.	O

#	O
art	B-CW
for	I-CW
art's	I-CW
sake	I-CW
(	O
stewart	O
,	O
gouldman	O
)	O
4	O
:	O
21	O

there	O
were	O
a	O
total	O
of	O
four	O
teams	O
from	O
iran	B-LOC
,	O
afghanistan	B-LOC
,	O
pakistan	B-LOC
and	O
oman	B-LOC
.	O

catherine	B-CW
the	I-CW
great	I-CW
(	O
tv	O
film	O
,	O
1996	O
)	O
,	O
as	O
peter	B-PER
iii	I-PER
of	I-PER
russia	I-PER

it	O
is	O
roughly	O
a	O
15	O
minute	O
train	O
journey	O
from	O
shibuya	B-LOC
station	I-LOC
.	O

demonstrators	O
first	O
marched	O
to	O
bbc	B-CORP
headquarter	O
to	O
denounce	O
what	O
they	O
called	O
pro	O
israeli	O
bias	O
.	O

graham	O
left	O
to	O
begin	O
a	O
successful	O
nine	O
year	O
spell	O
as	O
arsenal	B-GRP
f.c.	I-GRP
manager	O
.	O

tottenham	O
were	O
also	O
hit	O
by	O
injuries	O
with	O
jonathan	B-PER
woodgate	I-PER
being	O
forced	O
off	O
after	O
14	O
minutes	O
.	O

wsb	O
tv	O
also	O
carried	O
some	O
american	B-CORP
broadcasting	I-CORP
company	I-CORP
shows	O
.	O

boadicea	O
,	O
a	O
group	O
by	O
john	B-PER
thomas	I-PER
;	O

he	O
telephoned	O
condoleezza	B-PER
rice	I-PER
urging	O
the	O
u.s.	O
government	O
not	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
war	O
without	O
a	O
resolution	O
from	O
the	O
united	B-GRP
nations	I-GRP
security	I-GRP
council	I-GRP
.	O

the	O
first	O
anime	O
series	O
was	O
licensed	O
by	O
media	B-CORP
blasters	I-CORP
.	O

asc	B-GRP
port	I-GRP
autonome	I-GRP
won	O
their	O
only	O
cup	O
title	O

during	O
the	O
era	O
of	O
8	O
and	O
16	O
bit	O
desktop	O
computers	O
another	O
common	O
source	O
of	O
floating	O
point	O
coprocessors	O
was	O
weitek	B-CORP
.	O

his	O
third	O
son	O
edward	O
charles	O
o	O
maley	O
bethune	O
(	O
1900	O
1985	O
)	O
,	O
was	O
also	O
a	O
cricketer	O
,	O
playing	O
for	O
felsted	B-GRP
school	I-GRP
.	O

eds	O
sponsored	O
the	O
premier	B-CORP
league	I-CORP
association	O
football	O
team	O
derby	B-GRP
county	I-GRP
f.c.	I-GRP
from	O
1998	O
to	O
2001	O
.	O

a	O
third	O
adaptation	O
was	O
released	O
in	O
1955	O
as	O
illegal	B-CW
starring	O
edward	B-PER
g.	I-PER
robinson	I-PER
.	O

she	O
auditioned	O
with	O
etta	B-PER
james	I-PER
hit	O
song	O
at	B-CW
last	I-CW
.	O

other	O
variations	O
of	O
this	O
type	O
of	O
business	O
include	O
hair	O
salons	O
and	O
spa	B-CORP
.	O

the	O
song	O
is	O
credited	O
to	O
jesse	B-PER
stone	I-PER
and	O
the	O
the	B-GRP
clovers	I-GRP
.	O

along	O
the	O
gradual	O
curve	O
,	O
the	O
toll	O
road	O
continues	O
on	O
a	O
ramp	O
exiting	O
to	O
the	O
left	O
from	O
the	O
kamikita	B-LOC
expressway	I-LOC
.	O

tobermory	O
is	O
known	O
for	O
the	O
variety	O
of	O
colours	O
that	O
the	O
houses	O
of	O
the	O
shore	O
front	O
are	O
painted	O
in	O
and	O
for	O
being	O
the	O
location	O
of	O
the	O
children	O
's	O
television	O
show	O
balamory	B-CW
.	O

balocco	O
produces	O
a	O
range	O
of	O
biscuit	B-PROD
.	O

he	O
is	O
also	O
credited	O
with	O
writing	O
the	O
theme	O
for	O
the	O
film	O
lolita	B-CW
in	O
1962	O
.	O

it	O
stars	O
yvette	B-PER
mimieux	I-PER
in	O
her	O
final	O
film	O
performance	O
.	O

the	O
natal	B-GRP
government	I-GRP
railways	I-GRP
places	O
five	O
ngr	B-PROD
class	I-PROD
k	I-PROD
0-4-0st	I-PROD
saddle	O
tank	O
locomotives	O
in	O
service	O
as	O
shunting	O
engines	O
.	O

laelia	O
gouldiana	O
is	O
now	O
only	O
found	O
and	O
grown	O
as	O
a	O
cultivated	O
ornamental	B-PROD
plant	I-PROD
.	O

it	O
can	O
thus	O
can	O
be	O
considered	O
a	O
natural	O
form	O
of	O
plastic	B-PROD
.	O

born	O
in	O
sydney	B-LOC
,	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
oldest	O
son	O
of	O
john	B-PER
george	I-PER
bourinot	I-PER
.	O

lópez	O
's	O
older	O
brother	O
,	O
jorge	B-PER
lópez	I-PER
montaña	I-PER
,	O
was	O
also	O
a	O
footballer	O
.	O

4	O
:	O
milena	B-PER
dravić	I-PER
(	O
1964	O
,	O
1966	O
,	O
1967	O
*	O
,	O
1969	O
)	O

éverton	B-PER
santos	I-PER
(	O
2011	O
–	O
2012	O
seongnam	B-GRP
fc	I-GRP
,	O
2014	O
–	O
2015	O
fc	B-GRP
seoul	I-GRP
,	O
2015	O
ulsan	B-GRP
hyundai	I-GRP
fc	I-GRP
)	O

among	O
those	O
generally	O
considered	O
the	O
most	O
famous	O
were	O
scientist	O
albert	B-PER
einstein	I-PER
and	O
philosopher	O
ludwig	B-PER
wittgenstein	I-PER
.	O

1998	O
cucciolo	B-CW
,	O
directed	O
by	O
neri	B-PER
parenti	I-PER

he	O
attended	O
a	O
secular	O
high	O
school	O
and	O
studied	O
law	O
at	O
the	O
jagiellonian	B-GRP
university	I-GRP
.	O

she	O
met	O
john	B-PER
llewellyn	I-PER
lewis	I-PER
,	O
whom	O
she	O
described	O
as	O
a	O
principal	O
force	O
pushed	O
franklin	B-PER
delano	I-PER
roosevelt	I-PER
left	O
.	O

russell	O
's	O
brother	O
tony	B-PER
dingwall	I-PER
is	O
also	O
a	O
professional	O
footballer	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
currently	O
play	O
alongside	O
each	O
other	O
at	O
elgin	B-GRP
city	I-GRP
f.c.	I-GRP
.	O

he	O
died	O
,	O
aged	O
77	O
,	O
in	O
amsterdam	B-LOC
.	O

it	O
is	O
a	O
member	O
of	O
the	O
solaris	B-PROD
urbino	I-PROD
city	O
bus	O
family	O
.	O

he	O
is	O
a	O
member	O
of	O
the	O
democratic	B-GRP
party	I-GRP
.	O

galway	B-GRP
gaa	I-GRP
defeated	O
waterford	B-GRP
gaa	I-GRP
for	O
the	O
very	O
first	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
senior	O
hurling	O
championship	O
.	O

he	O
also	O
helped	O
orchestrate	O
the	O
1986	O
introduction	O
of	O
a	O
postage	B-PROD
stamp	I-PROD
in	O
honor	O
of	O
duke	B-PER
ellington	I-PER
.	O

one	O
of	O
his	O
earliest	O
achievements	O
was	O
supplying	O
shoes	O
to	O
the	O
1923	O
ziegfeld	B-CW
follies	I-CW
production	O
.	O

there	O
are	O
also	O
ruins	O
of	O
a	O
coarse	O
stone	O
temple	B-LOC
on	O
the	O
island	O
measuring	O
around	O
square	O
with	O
a	O
plastered	O
altar	O
for	O
fire	O
in	O
the	O
centre	O
.	O

her	O
brother	O
was	O
actor	O
dan	B-PER
dailey	I-PER
.	O

in	O
the	O
1970s	O
,	O
the	O
casual	O
style	O
was	O
born	O
,	O
and	O
loose	O
jumpsuit	B-PROD
and	O
pants	O
replaced	O
the	O
dresses	O
.	O

he	O
played	O
for	O
the	O
pittsburgh	B-GRP
pirates	I-GRP
in	O
1927	O
.	O

snapp	O
agreed	O
with	O
the	O
boos	O
of	O
the	O
crowd	O
and	O
began	O
playing	O
three	B-CW
blind	I-CW
mice	I-CW
.	O

before	O
1945	O
the	O
area	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
germany	B-LOC
.	O

another	O
definition	O
(	O
from	O
noah	B-PER
webster	I-PER
)	O
:	O
nearly	O
an	O
inch	O
.	O

the	O
game	O
received	O
positive	O
reviews	O
,	O
with	O
critics	O
comparing	O
the	O
game	O
to	O
the	O
micro	B-CW
machines	I-CW
and	O
mario	B-CW
kart	I-CW
series	O
.	O

for	O
example	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
potential	O
difference	O
across	O
a	O
capacitor	B-PROD
is	O
halved	O
,	O
the	O
quantity	O
of	O
charge	O
stored	O
by	O
that	O
capacitor	O
will	O
also	O
be	O
halved	O
.	O

the	O
scientific	O
works	O
of	O
the	O
national	B-GRP
university	I-GRP
“odesa	I-GRP
law	I-GRP
academy”	I-GRP
,	O
2003	O
.	O

there	O
was	O
an	O
engine	O
shed	O
at	O
beattock	B-LOC
which	O
had	O
banking	O
locomotives	O
on	O
standby	O
twenty	O
four	O
hours	O
per	O
day	O
to	O
minimise	O
train	O
delays	O
.	O

in	O
this	O
particular	O
case	O
,	O
british	B-CORP
leyland	I-CORP
charged	O
£	O
150	O
to	O
any	O
importer	O
in	O
the	O
continent	O
that	O
required	O
a	O
certificate	O
to	O
drive	O
cars	O
in	O
the	O
united	B-LOC
kingdom	I-LOC
.	O

